<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
	xmlns:amzn="https://amazon.com/ospublishing/1.0/"
>

<channel>
	<title>Footwear NewsFootwear News</title>
	<link>https://footwearnews.com</link>
		<description>Shoe News and Fashion Trends</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 13:12:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en</language>
	<amzn:rssVersion>1.0</amzn:rssVersion>
	<item>
		<title>The Best Hiking Socks</title>
		<author>Samantha Peters</author>		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 22:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<link>https://footwearnews.com/2019/shop/socks/best-hiking-socks-amazon-1202808304/</link>
					<amzn:heroImage>https://pmcfootwearnews.files.wordpress.com/2019/07/best-hiking-socks.jpg</amzn:heroImage>
							<amzn:heroImageCaption>Shutterstock</amzn:heroImageCaption>
					<amzn:indexContent>False</amzn:indexContent>
		<amzn:products>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07117PVS8/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Danish Endurance Merino Wool Hiking Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[These Danish Endurance hiking socks are naturally temperature-regulating and moisture-wicking.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Overall]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B01EIVJ4PI/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Seoulstory7 Women's Hiking Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[These socks are designed to minimize friction and support the arch of your foot.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Notable Pick]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B01JIPV54W/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Yuedge Women's Hiking Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[These socks are ideal for colder conditions and come in a variety of vibrant colors.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Bang for Your Buck]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07F3FFTMK/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Alvada Merino Wool Hiking Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[These Alvada socks will keep your feet cool and dry during the most intense hikes.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Honorable Mention]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B009Y9QCCS/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[People Socks Merino Wool Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[These socks will help to cancel out any odors and keep you comfortable for hours on your feet.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Also Consider]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B01INNMQ98/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[MIRMARU Men's Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[These socks are engineered to prevent blisters and keep feet the perfect temperature.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best for Blister Prevention]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B000HZXY4W/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Smartwool Men's Hiking Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Smartwool’s hiking socks are designed to maintain their softness and shape through many seasons.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Splurge-Worthy Pick]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
				</amzn:products>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A good pair of hiking socks is a must for tackling trails. Naturally, you’ll want to choose a style that’s soft and moisture-wicking in order to prevent chafing and blisters. Depending on the season, you can also choose from socks of varying thickness to help keep feet extra warm or cool. Not sure where to start? We’re here to help. Below, we’ve rounded up the best hiking socks for men and women to add to your wardrobe now, from plush cotton styles to options made with adaptive merino wool that are perfect for all sorts of weather conditions. Read on to shop them all.</p>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07117PVS8/" />
	</div>
	<p>These ultra-durable socks are made with temperature-regulating merino wool to keep you cool in summer and warm in winter. They're even a favorite among Danish mountaineer and trail runner Rasmus Kragh, who has successfully tackled Mount Everest.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> These socks also amp up comfort via moderate cushioning in the heel and forefoot and seamless toe design to prevent blisters. They also feature ribbed support in the leg, so they won’t bunch or slip down and cause uncomfortable rubbing inside your hiking boot. On top of all that, they’re made with a high-density knit to withstand tough and frequent wear and come in sizes for both men and women.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> These tend to run large and should be line dried.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B01EIVJ4PI/" />
	</div>
	<p>Great for everything from rigorous hikes to everyday walks, these cotton-blend socks offer lightweight support in a range of fun, colorful designs.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> For added comfort, they feature cushioning in the ball of the foot and heel, arch support and a compression top to prevent the socks from slipping down. They come as a value pack with two or five socks. Plus, they’re machine washable and dryer safe for easy maintenance.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> Some users may find these too warm to wear on summer hikes and the toe seam is uncomfortable.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B01JIPV54W/" />
	</div>
	<p>If your feet tend to get sweaty, these socks are a must. They’re equipped with breathable mesh and antimicrobial fabric to help keep your feet cool and fresh-smelling.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> The socks also feature cushioning in the heel and forefoot and a lightly compressive top with a double ribbed design on the cuff for extra security. What’s more, they’re reinforced with terry cloth on the heel and toe areas to reduce wear and tear. They’re also fairly thick, so they can be worn in cooler conditions, although maybe not sub-freezing temperatures. They come as a value pack of five and are also available in a variety of bright colors.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> These are not dryer-safe (they tend to shrink if not lined dry).</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07F3FFTMK/" />
	</div>
	<p>These socks are also made with super-soft, breathable merino wool, which regulates the body's temperature to keep your feet from overheating.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>They're blended with nylon to ensure they're itch-free and polyester for increased durability. Meanwhile, a hint of spandex adds stretch for ultimate comfort. The footbed is fully cushioned to absorb impact. These come in a value pack of 3.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>If you have larger calves, they may feel slightly tight.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B009Y9QCCS/" />
	</div>
	<p>These merino wool socks have smooth toe construction to prevent irritation and shaped cushioning in the footbed for extra comfort.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>Elasticized arches offer support and stability. The toes and heels are reinforced for long-lasting wear. They come in a pack of 4 with various colors.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>They may shrink if left in the drier for too long.</p>
<p><strong></strong></p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B01INNMQ98/" />
	</div>
	<p>These socks feature a breathable, moisture-wicking blend of combed cotton and polyester with just a bit of spandex for improved stretch.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>These socks are reinforced with high-density fibers and pile cushioning underfoot to prevent blisters and boost overall comfort. Elastic in the arch offers added support. They come in multiple sizes and colors. This value pack includes five pairs.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>They may shed a bit.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B000HZXY4W/" />
	</div>
	<p>These Smartwool merino wool socks are blended with nylon and elastic for improved durability and fit.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>An arch brace holds the sock in place and adds additional support while a flat-knit toe seam minimizes friction. Moderate cushioning underfoot absorbs impact. Mesh zones throughout promote breathability. They come in a range of sizes and colors.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>They may run big.</p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Best Footrests to Support Achy Feet and Legs</title>
		<author>Samantha Peters</author>		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 22:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<link>https://footwearnews.com/2019/shop/health/best-foot-rests-support-1202803146/</link>
					<amzn:heroImage>https://pmcfootwearnews.files.wordpress.com/2019/07/best-foot-rests-amazon.jpg</amzn:heroImage>
							<amzn:heroImageCaption>Amazon</amzn:heroImageCaption>
					<amzn:indexContent>False</amzn:indexContent>
		<amzn:products>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07C8836PN/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[ErgoFoam Ergonomic Footrest]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[This plush footrest provides firm support for your feet while helping improve your posture.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Footrest Cushion]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07QHBS21X/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Hokeki Footrest]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[This footrest is soft-yet-firm and easy to clean.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Also Consider Footrest Cushion]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B01DN8TG46/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[AmazonBasics Under Desk Footrest]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[This AmazonBasics footrest is designed to help minimize fatigue and increase circulation.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Under the Desk Footrest]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07L3RVF7C/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Huanuo Under Desk Footrest]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[This footrest is adjustable with multiple tilt angles and height settings.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Also Consider for Under the Desk]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B01BRU9CDW/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Office Ottoman Footrest]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[The Office Ottoman can travel with you anywhere you need extra support.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Most Versatile]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07PGLBCFG/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Everlasting Comfort Office Footrest]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[This Everlasting Comfort footrest is perfect for the office and flights.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Memory Foam Cushion Footrest]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07N1QCJGZ/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[StrongTek Footrest]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[This StrongTek footrest features a wide, well-balanced design.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Wooden Footrest]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
				</amzn:products>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sitting in a desk chair or airplane seat for long periods of time can cause your legs and feet to become stiff, sore and swell due to lack of circulation. Footrests offer a great solution to the problem. Available in plastic, wood and foam styles, they elevate your feet to improve blood flow and prevent fatigue. They also provide firm support to encourage better posture, which in turn can help reduce soreness in the back, legs and knees.</p>
<p>Even beyond their health benefits, footrests are great for petite individuals whose feet may not hit the ground while sitting. Many are often tilt-adjustable to accommodate a range of body sizes and heights. From sleek options for under the desk to slings designed specifically for in-flight travel, we&#8217;ve rounded up the best footrests on the market to fit a range of needs and budgets. Read on to shop them all.</p>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07C8836PN/" />
	</div>
	<p>Ideal for work, home or travel, this velvety cushion can be used with bare or socked feet and is super-soft to the touch.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> The design comes with a nonslip bottom to keep the unit firmly in place, plus a removable cover that's machine washable for easy cleanup. The crescent-shaped cushion has a flat base; it can also be flipped over to become a rocker if you prefer to keep feet moving. At 3.9 inches tall, it provides just the right amount of elevation to maximize comfort for people of all heights. It's also much lighter to carry than other freestanding styles, making it great to carry when you're on the go.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>Due to its plush exterior, the unit may make feet warm — so it may not be for summer use.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07QHBS21X/" />
	</div>
	<p>This footrest features ergonomic pedals made of comfortable Velboa and 30D high-density sponge.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>It has a non-slip bottom and the cover is machine washable.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>The firmness may decrease after months of putting pressure on it. <strong></strong></p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B01DN8TG46/" />
	</div>
	<p>Designed to be used with or without shoes, this plastic under-desk footrest tilts back and forth so your legs can stretch as you work.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> All you have to do is apply light pressure to the unit to adjust it to your desired positioning so you can perform everything from lower-leg to full-leg stretches. The design also features a t<span class="a-list-item">extured surface for a massagelike feel on the soles of bare or socked feet. While looks aren't necessarily crucial when it comes to footrests, this design is sleek enough to easily blend in with your decor </span>— <span class="a-list-item">complete with a low-profile silhouette finished in black. </span></p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>The height of the unit isn't adjustable, so it may be too low to the ground to support people with shorter legs (it's only 3.4 inches tall, as opposed to the average 3.9-4-inches for many styles).</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07L3RVF7C/" />
	</div>
	<p>This model has a textured surface made up of geometric circular bumps for enhanced stress reduction.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> It comes fully assembled. It offers three adjustable height positions and tilts from -30 degrees to +30 degrees, allowing you to find the most comfortable angle for you.</p>
<p><span style="font-family:-apple-system, BlinkMacSystemFont, Segoe UI, Roboto, Oxygen-Sans, Ubuntu, Cantarell, Helvetica Neue, sans-serif;"><strong>Cons:</strong> It may slide around a bit.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-family:-apple-system, BlinkMacSystemFont, Segoe UI, Roboto, Oxygen-Sans, Ubuntu, Cantarell, Helvetica Neue, sans-serif;"><strong></strong> </span></p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B01BRU9CDW/" />
	</div>
	<p>Specifically designed to provide ample clearance under desks, this supportive, four-inch tall cushion could work just about anywhere. Plus, it's made of an antimicrobial and hypoallergenic foam to prevent odor buildup.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> The bottom of the unit features a microbead tread to subtly massage feet and prevent the unit from shifting when placed upright. Meanwhile, the design can also be flipped over to act as a roller. To help keep the velour fabric fresh, the cover is removable and machine washable.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> The zipper is on the bottom of the unit, and it might dig into hardwood floors.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07PGLBCFG/" />
	</div>
	<p>This footrest is made with 100% memory foam and has an orthopedic teardrop design, which places your feet and legs in a more comfortable and ergonomically correct position.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>A non-slip gel rubber bottom ensures it always stays in place. The ultra-soft, durable velour cover is removable and machine washable.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>Some may prefer a firmer footrest.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07N1QCJGZ/" />
	</div>
	<p>This footrest features curved feet with anti-slip grips on the bottom that let it roll and tilt without slipping or sliding.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> It's crafted with heavy-duty Lauan hardwood plywood for long-lasting strength and reliable durability.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>The grippy surface may be hard to clean.</p>
<p><strong></strong></p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Best Foot Warmers You&#8217;ll Ever Need</title>
		<author>Charlie Carballo</author>		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 22:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<link>https://footwearnews.com/2019/shop/health/best-foot-warmers-1202832830/</link>
					<amzn:heroImage>https://pmcfootwearnews.files.wordpress.com/2019/09/feet-blanket-warmer.jpg</amzn:heroImage>
							<amzn:heroImageCaption></amzn:heroImageCaption>
					<amzn:indexContent>False</amzn:indexContent>
		<amzn:products>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07B957W66/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Proaller Heating Pad]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[This heated foot warmer is large enough to fit two pairs of feet.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Top Pick]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07HMG3SJF/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Doneco King Size Heating Pad]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[You won’t stay cold for long with Doneco’s heating pad, which gets your feet warm in seconds. It’s safe for snuggling with your pets.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Bang for Your Buck]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07CSD6XBB/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Happy Heat Electric Foot Warmer]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Happy Heat’s electric foot warmer stays heated for up to five hours.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Also Consider]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B0013V6PDG/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Cozy Products TT Toasty Toes Foot Warmer]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[This product is engineered as an ergonomic foot warmer that serves as a space heater and foot rest.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Under the Desk Foot Heater]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07SG4VBTY/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Snailax 2-in-1 Shiatsu Foot and Back Massager]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[This heater is also essentially a full-body massager. It’s lightweight and totally portable.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Design]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B082DGNM6T/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[HotHands Insole Foot Warmers]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[These foot warmers are easily activated by air, last for hours and are conveniently disposable.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Disposable Foot Warmers]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07MHGKKVD/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Terra-Warm Microwave Toes]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[These foot-warming booties have a soothing scent and couldn’t be easier to use.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Bootie-Style Foot Warmers]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
				</amzn:products>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cold feet will be a nuisance come winter. Your piggies might feel numb or hard or just plain icy to the touch. The problem typically occurs when temperatures drop, which makes your body respond by pumping blood to the most vital organs. This causes a change in blood flow to areas like your feet and hands, which results in the type of cold feeling you want to avoid. That&#8217;s why maintaining a bit of warmth from ankle to heel will help keep your feet comfortable. As a bonus, when your feet are warm, other parts of your body reap the benefits, too. Heating products can also improve relaxation, so invest in a foot warmer. Let&#8217;s not forget that incorporating a foot warmer can help you save money as you might consider turning off room and home heaters. Below, we&#8217;ve curated some of the best foot warmers on the market with you in mind.</p>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07B957W66/" />
	</div>
	<p>At 22 inches wide and 21 inches deep, it's big enough to accommodate two pairs of feet. The 15-inch cover featuring ultra-plush fabric protects your shins from cold air.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> Both sides are constructed from luxuriously soft, thick flannel that is exceptionally durable and warm. The cord is 10-feet long and a 2-hour auto-off helps you save energy and prevent excessive heating. It has 3 heat settings.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> Some may find since it's so roomy, cold air can get in sometimes.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07HMG3SJF/" />
	</div>
	<p>There's room for two people (that's four feet) under this product's roomy pad pocket. It will ease sore muscles and can be used around different parts of your body, including the neck, shoulders, back and legs.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> A mixture of micromink and polyester means the material is extra-soft. This heating pad comes with an LCD controller with four different levels. It automatically shuts off after continuous use for 2 hours to prevent overheating. Best of all, it comes with a 30-day satisfaction guarantee.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>Though it's safe for the washing machine, consider hand-washing to maintain quality.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07CSD6XBB/" />
	</div>
	<p>This electric foot warmer has a soft fleece cover and heats up when you plug it in for just 12 to 15 minutes. It comes with water in a pre-sealed pouch that heats up, from 140 degrees to 158 degrees Fahrenheit.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>This also has a built-in auto shut-off function and a non-skid bottom. It fits women's feet up to size 14 and men's size 13. It should stay warm for up to 5 hours at a time.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>The water may get too hot for some so you should wear socks.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B0013V6PDG/" />
	</div>
	<p>The foot warmer is an energy-efficient, low-watt device that warms your feet just as well as its competitors, but won't overload your electric circuits with its cost-cutting tech.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> Three adjustable positions allow you to use it as a heater when positioned upright, and it can also be used as a foot stool or heated mat. You can use it with your shoes on or barefoot. The design is attractive enough to use in the office or at home.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> Some thick shoes might not be able to transfer the heat to your feet as well as minimalist options.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07SG4VBTY/" />
	</div>
	<p>This heat therapy foot massager is made with a super-soft polyester top cover that's removable and has a non-slip bottom.</p>
<p><strong style="font-family:-apple-system, BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen-Sans, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;">Pros: </strong><span style="font-family:-apple-system, BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen-Sans, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;">It has</span><span style="font-family:-apple-system, BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen-Sans, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;"> eight rotating shiatsu rollers that offer a deep tissue kneading massage. The top cover can be detached so you can use the unit as a heating pad, back massager or heated seat cushion. It also comes in a PU leather option.</span></p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> It automatically shuts off after just 15 minutes.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B082DGNM6T/" />
	</div>
	<p>You simply shake these to activate them and they'll warm up in 15-30 minutes.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>They're easily disposable with no ingredients that will harm the environment. They come in packs of 2, 3, 5 or 16.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>You may need to wear looser boots with these.</p>
<p><strong></strong></p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07MHGKKVD/" />
	</div>
	<p>You simply put these plush booties in the microwave for 60 seconds and they provide warmth for the whole foot.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>They're scented with lavender and fit adult foot sizes 6-10.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>They're not washable.</p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Best Boot Dryers for Faster Results</title>
		<author>Samantha Peters</author>		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 16:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<link>https://footwearnews.com/2019/shop/boots/best-boot-dryers-fans-1202806357/</link>
					<amzn:heroImage>https://pmcfootwearnews.files.wordpress.com/2019/10/odor-stop-boot-dryer.jpg</amzn:heroImage>
							<amzn:heroImageCaption>Amazon</amzn:heroImageCaption>
					<amzn:indexContent>False</amzn:indexContent>
		<amzn:products>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B014SB2X0G/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[MaxxDry Heavy Duty Boot Dryer]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[This slim boot dryer is made to dry all types of shoes in as little as an hour, from running sneakers to ski boots.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Overall]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B010A5J5FU/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[DryGuy DX Forced Air Boot Dryer]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[This machine should thoroughly dry gloves, boots and more, while being surprisingly quiet.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best for Noise Reduction]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B001J4HQ76/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Peet Original 2-Shoe Electric Shoe and Boot Dryer]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[You won’t have to worry about keeping this two-shoe dryer from Peet plugged in all day; it’s particularly energy-efficient and designed to be quick-drying.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Energy Saver]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B011AJ828Q/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Kendal Boots Dryer]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Mount Kendal’s dryer for space-saving use.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best for Smaller Spaces]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B06XCSGKXK/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Manledio Portable Electric Shoe Dryer]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Pack up Manledio’s foldable shoe dryer for on-the-go use.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best for Travel]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B00AYJKBHE/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[JobSite Original Boot Dryer]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Dry your heaviest pairs of boots with JobSite’s dryer.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best for Heavy-Duty Boots]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07K4W38PV/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[OdorStop Boot and Shoe Dryer]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[This unit will dry your shoes and kill odors at the same time.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Dual Function Design]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
				</amzn:products>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Wet boots are uncomfortable, but they can take up to a full day to air-dry. Thankfully, boot dryers are a great alternative. These handy machines can dry boots or shoes in just a few hours, so you&#8217;re ready to comfortably take on your next adventure. The best options operate with a fan, which makes them especially efficient and helps keep foul-smelling bacteria at bay. Many are built to dry two to four pairs at once and can work with a range of materials like leather, fleece and neoprene. Of course, check the particular dryer to ensure your shoes are compatible with the unit. You can also opt for a compact, foldable option if your floor space is limited. Considering all this, we&#8217;ve compiled some of the best boot dryers we could find in every category.</p>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B014SB2X0G/" />
	</div>
	<p>The unit features two removable extension tubes to fit boots up to 16 inches tall. For especially fast results, the dryer can spew out heat up to 105 degrees Fahrenheit.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> One of the key selling points of this item is its noticeably compact design, which makes it easier to store in your home. It also comes with a three-hour timer so you can set the dry time to your liking, plus an optional heat switch that can dry items with or without heat. In addition to drying footwear, the machine is also safe to use on liners and clothes (with no shrinkage or damage to delicate items). It comes with a six-inch power cord for easy maneuverability and a one-year warranty, just in case you're not fully satisfied with your purchase.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>This unit tends to be noisy.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B010A5J5FU/" />
	</div>
	<p>Like the Maxxdry, this option includes two removable extension tubes to accommodate boots up to 16 inches tall, a three-hour timer and a heat or no-heat switch.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> It's also able to heat up to 105 degrees Fahrenheit and is safe to use on clothes and liners. Plus, it comes with a one-year warranty in case the unit is damaged.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> The unit tends to tip over when used with heavy ski boots. Items tend to take longer to dry with this machine, typically within a few hours.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B001J4HQ76/" />
	</div>
	<p>This two-shoe dryer is safe to use on all footwear. It's made to fully dry shoes within three to eight hours, all while using less electricity than a standard light bulb thanks to thermal convention.</p>
<p><strong>Pros</strong>: It's also designed to be silent and comes with a 25-year warranty.</p>
<p><strong>Cons</strong>: It doesn't come with an on/off switch.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B011AJ828Q/" />
	</div>
	<p>Kendal's dryer can be set with an up to three hours timer with low and high-temperature modes. It uses tubes with warm air and aroma active carbon to reduce odor.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>This dryer can dry 2 pairs of shoes at the same time and also comes with a separate glove drying apparatus for versatile use. It weighs 3.5-pounds and comes with an added wall mount so it is lightweight and takes up less space in smaller areas.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> It can't be mounted or placed near any flammable object like cushions or curtains.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B06XCSGKXK/" />
	</div>
	<p>With a constant 106 degree Farhenheit temperature, this dryer airs without causing damage to your shoe with an adjustable distance between the two stretched brackets.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> It dries most materials including leather, rubber, PVC, neoprene, cloth, fleece, felt, canvas, synthetics and fabrics. It has a portable, fold-up design so you can bring it along with you to your next outdoor event from camping to sports.</p>
<p><strong style="font-family:-apple-system, BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen-Sans, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;">Cons:</strong> The brand advises to not put "soaked" or "dripping wet" shoes directly on the dryer.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B00AYJKBHE/" />
	</div>
	<p>JobSite's dual-tube shoe dryer dries bulky, damp boots in eight hours and wet shoes overnight with no motor or moving parts for silent usage.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> This drier uses warm thermal air that rises naturally as to not shrink the boot. It naturally deodorizes and prevents odors caused by perspiration. The sturdy base allows you to dry insulated boots, work boots, rain boots and more with a two-year warranty as well.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> The dry cycle time may be too long for anyone in need of dry shoes in a hurry.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07K4W38PV/" />
	</div>
	<p>OdorStop's dryer is designed to permanently remove odor from shoes with featuring an added deodorizer function.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> This dryer can dry a single pair of boots and features adjustable tubes to dry boots of different heights. It also includes a high output fan and a three-hour timer with an optional constant setting. The heat and deodorizer function can be used separately, so you can save energy if you just need to freshen up already dry pairs.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> The brand warns that the deodorizer may omit a strong smell and should be used when you're not in the room.</p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Best Shoe Deodorizers to Eliminate the Stink</title>
		<author>Samantha Peters</author>		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 16:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<link>https://footwearnews.com/2019/shop/shoes/best-shoe-deodorizers-smelly-feet-1202772086/</link>
					<amzn:heroImage>https://pmcfootwearnews.files.wordpress.com/2019/04/smell-shoes-best-shoe-deodarizers.jpg</amzn:heroImage>
							<amzn:heroImageCaption>Shutterstock/kitzcorner</amzn:heroImageCaption>
					<amzn:indexContent>False</amzn:indexContent>
		<amzn:products>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B013TSRYUS/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Lumi Outdoors Natural Shoe Deodorizer Spray]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Effectively mask odors with one to two sprays.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Top Pick]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B01BSO9K7K/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Sof Sole Fresh Fogger Shoe Spray]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[The design of this spray bottle allows for versatile use with various shoe silhouettes.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Design]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B00O2DQO4C/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Foot Sense Foot and Shoe Powder]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Get long-term results with Foot Sense’s strong powder.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best for Long-Lasting Results]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B00KA716II/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Elite Sportz Shoe Deodorizer]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Moisturize and deodorize at the same time with this spray.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best for Dry Feet]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B01LYCSJM8/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Sprayzee Shoe Deodorizer Spray]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Protect sensitive skin while eliminating odors thanks to Sprayzee’s deodorizer.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best for Sensitive Skin]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B00B0N281A/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Rocket Pure Shoe Deodorizer]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Choose your ideal scent from Rocket Pure’s many options.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Scent Variety]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B0719KPLD9/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[NonScents Shoe Deodorizer]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Throw these deodorizers into your shoes for effective results.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Shoe Deodorizer Inserts]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
				</amzn:products>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Stinky feet can be annoying and embarrassing. They&#8217;re caused by bacteria and fungi, which can fester in shoes and leave behind an unpleasant stench. Thankfully, all hope is not lost if your favorite pairs have become odiferous. A deodorizer will neutralize and prevent foul odor from forming, so you&#8217;ll never have to worry about taking your shoes off in public again. To help make your shopping a little easier, we’ve rounded up some of the best options on the market for instant freshness — including sprays, powders and solid deodorizers you can pop in your bag on the go. Read on to discover them all.</p>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B013TSRYUS/" />
	</div>
	<p>This maximum strength spray features essential oils to fight bacteria that cause odors.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>Available in a refreshing lemon and eucalyptus scent, this spray doesn't leave behind a residue and only takes one to two sprays per shoe to effectively mask odors.</p>
<p><strong style="font-family:-apple-system, BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen-Sans, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;">Cons: </strong>The smell may be overpowering at first.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B01BSO9K7K/" />
	</div>
	<p>The nozzle on Sof Sole's bottle allows for two different ways to spray your shoes to get unique angles and hard to reach crevices.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>The formula of this spray does not discolor or leave behind film or residue for long-lasting coverage. It is safe on mesh, leather, canvas, suede and more.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>Bottle may be smaller in person than it appears online.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B00O2DQO4C/" />
	</div>
	<p>This all-natural powder is safe enough to use directly on feet and great for those who want a scent-free option.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:  </strong>Made with zinc oxide, which prevents bacteria growth and blisters from forming, this powder is able to last up to six months with repeated application. Customers are guaranteed a full refund if the product doesn’t perform as promised.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>Powder is hard to spread evenly and shouldn’t be used in open-toed shoes as it leaves behind a residue.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B00KA716II/" />
	</div>
	<p>Elite Sportz uses seven pure essential oils and 11 helpful herbs and botanicals to create this stench-reducing spray.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>This spray is also a moisturizer that goes to work controlling odors and soothing dry, cracked soles with 100% non-toxic ingredients.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> The smell may be overpowered by the peppermint ingredient.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B01LYCSJM8/" />
	</div>
	<p>Made with 12 powerhouse essential oils and natural enzymes like apple cider vinegar, peppermint oil, tea tree oil and eucalyptus oil, Sprayzee's deodorizer is meant to eliminate any foul odor from shoes.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> This aluminum-free and paraben-free product is easy on sensitive skin and uses essential oils and enzymes to alter odors on a molecular level rather than just cover them up.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> The spray nozzle may clog if not cleaned properly.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B00B0N281A/" />
	</div>
	<p>Rocket Pure's deodorizer features natural and non-toxic ingredients with a lifetime guarantee policy.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> This spray comes with options of mint, cedar or lemon scents so you can find the smell that most appeals to you to fix your stinky shoes.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> The brand recommends to shake well before use as they use natural ingredients and some separation may occur.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B0719KPLD9/" />
	</div>
	<p>These deodorizers are easy to use and can be simply dropped into the shoe of your choice and left for all-day work</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>They can eliminate odor for over six months and can be used in anything from a boot to a sneaker and more.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> These might not sit properly in sandals on thong flip flops.</p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Best Shoe Cleaners for Keeping Pairs Pristine</title>
		<author>Samantha Peters</author>		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 15:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<link>https://footwearnews.com/2019/shop/shoes/best-shoe-cleaner-products-1202817776/</link>
					<amzn:heroImage>https://pmcfootwearnews.files.wordpress.com/2019/08/best-shoe-cleaner.jpg</amzn:heroImage>
							<amzn:heroImageCaption>Shutterstock</amzn:heroImageCaption>
					<amzn:indexContent>False</amzn:indexContent>
		<amzn:products>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B00D12KGVW/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Jason Markk Premium Shoe Cleaner]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[This high-quality set works on a range of materials and is even a favorite among sneakerheads for keeping expensive pairs in tip-top condition.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Multipurpose Shoe Cleaner]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B00A7NDT3A/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Pink Miracle Shoe Cleaner]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[This classic option has been around since 1985, offering pristine cleaning for shoes and more items.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Honorable Mention Multipurpose Shoe Cleaner]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B007CAT2R8/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Reshoevn8r Shoe &amp; Sneaker Cleaner]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Clean your shoes with ease thanks to this all-natural formula with an easy push cap design.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Also Consider Multipurpose Shoe Cleaner]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B01ED8P3HO/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Angelus Easy Cleaner Kit]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Prep your shoes for dye with this cleaning kit.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best for Dye Prep]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07LGVZLP9/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Lexol Conditioner Cleaner Kit]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Lexol’s kit helps you clean and condition even your most worn-out leather footwear.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Leather Shoe Cleaner]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07KGKNHBW/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Grandma's Secret Sneaker Cleaner Spray]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Restore your sneakers back to prime condition with Grandma’s spray.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Spray Shoe Cleaner]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07D349D77/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Combat Cleaner Shoe Cleaner Kit]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Clean, deodorize and protect your shoes with this four-piece kit.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Most Expansive Set]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
				</amzn:products>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When cleaning your shoes, a simple soap and water treatment often won&#8217;t do. For finishes like a supple leather, suede and mesh, you&#8217;ll want to opt for a special shoe cleaner that will remove tough stains and renew the finish without damaging it. Below, we&#8217;ve rounded up the best shoe cleaners to suit a range of needs. We&#8217;ve included solutions perfect for all types of materials as well as one that specifically clean and restores leather. Our list also includes handy sets complete with formula and a brush, as well as spray nozzle options that allow for more even application during an all-over clean. Read on to find your perfect match.</p>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B00D12KGVW/" />
	</div>
	<p>The all-natural formula is suitable for practically any finish, including leather, suede, nubuck, nylon and mesh cotton. The brush features soft hog bristles that are gentle enough for removing loose dirt on shoes and assisting in removing stains. <b></b></p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> To make you feel even better about your purchase, the solution is also biodegradable, causing less harm to the environment. The solution is meant to clean up to 100 pairs of sneakers so you can get a better bang for your buck.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> Some users may find the brush to be slightly small.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B00A7NDT3A/" />
	</div>
	<p>This timeless cleaner is free of harsh chemicals. It works on suede, leather, vinyl, nubuck, polyester shoes, but is also designed to be used on purses, upholstery, gym bags and more of the same materials.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> A brush is also included in the set for full-on maintenance. The solution comes in an 8 oz. bottle, with only a dime size needed on every application for extended use.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> Some users may find this solution stains popular Nike Flyknit and Adidas Primeknit sneakers.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B007CAT2R8/" />
	</div>
	<p>Made from coconut, jojoba and other natural oils, Reshoevn8r's cleaner comes in a concentrated 8-ounce bottle.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> This cleaner works on leather, canvas, suede, mesh and many more fabrics with a simple push cap that allows for speedy application of the solution.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>Bottle may leak if not closed properly.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B01ED8P3HO/" />
	</div>
	<p>Angelus' cleaner kit is meant to wipe your shoes clean from surface-level dirt before dying them to cover scratches or marks.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>This kit comes with the solution, a microfiber towel and a premium cleaning brush for variable use on different types of shoes, working best on leather, suede, nubuck and more.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> It doesn't work as effectively on deeper stains.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07LGVZLP9/" />
	</div>
	<p>Lexol provides one bottle of all-leather deep cleaner an 8 oz. bottle of all-leather deep conditioner and two premium applicator sponges.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> This set has all you need to both clean and condition your leather shoes to lift dirt and oil and bring worn-out leather back to its original state.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> This is meant solely for leather products so you may need to buy separate cleaners for other types of shoes.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07KGKNHBW/" />
	</div>
	<p>This pack comes with two bottles of premium sneaker cleaning spray to bring your favorite kicks back to life.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> This spray is environmentally responsible with no chlorine and no bleach that is safe enough to use on rubber, cloth, canvas and leather sneakers.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> You must remove your sneakers' laces before using this spray.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07D349D77/" />
	</div>
	<p>Find everything you need to fix up your shoes in Combat Cleaner's three spray bottle kit with an added shoe brush.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> This set includes a shoe deodorizer to eliminate bad smells, a shoe cleaner to remove dirt and stains from your shoes and a shoe shield to repel oils and water.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>The cleaner is not meant for suede shoes.</p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>These Dog-Themed Socks Are Paws-itively Adorable</title>
		<author>Allie Fasanella</author>		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 15:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<link>https://footwearnews.com/2020/shop/socks/dog-patterned-animal-socks-amazon-1202904493/</link>
					<amzn:heroImage>https://pmcfootwearnews.files.wordpress.com/2020/01/gold-toe-mens-printed-novelty-graphic-fashion-dress-crew-socks.jpg</amzn:heroImage>
							<amzn:heroImageCaption>Amazon</amzn:heroImageCaption>
					<amzn:indexContent>False</amzn:indexContent>
		<amzn:products>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07X2M4SLW/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Cavertin Women's Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[These socks not only have a fun dog print but they also contain a funny hidden message on the soles.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best for Women]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07B96FVHM/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Gold Toe Men's Dress Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Guys will love these sturdy socks covered with dogs playing frisbee.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best for Men]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B01731388E/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Carahere Women's Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[This value pack features styles with an adorable dachshund print.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Bang for Your Buck]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
				</amzn:products>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If you&#8217;re obsessed with dogs, like much of the world is, why not show your passion for them with your socks? A pair of fun pup patterned socks is sure to make you smile or make a great gift for animal lovers. Since there are a wide selection of dog-print socks on the market, we did some research to narrow down the choices. Ahead, our favorite crew styles for women and men. Each of our picks features a soft, durable fabric blend with an ideal amount of stretch to provide an ultra-comfortable, foot-hugging fit.</p>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07X2M4SLW/" />
	</div>
	<p>These socks are made with premium combed cotton as well as nylon and a hint of spandex. The soles feature a hidden message that reads: "I can't get up right now. The dog is on my lap."</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>They're designed to fit women's shoe sizes 6-12. They come packaged in a nice gift box.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>Some may find they run a tad small.<strong></strong></p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07B96FVHM/" />
	</div>
	<p>These blue socks are made with soft, strong modal rayon and feature an all-over print of black dogs playing frisbee.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>They have a long-lasting reinforced toe and fit men's foot sizes 6-12.5.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>These may be slightly longer on some.<strong></strong></p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B01731388E/" />
	</div>
	<p>These socks come in gray with blue accents and cream with orange details. Both feature dachshunds wearing sweaters throughout.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>You get two pairs of socks in a single pack.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>These may be a bit tight on some.<strong></strong></p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>These Socks Are Perfect for Corgi Lovers</title>
		<author>Allie Fasanella</author>		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 15:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<link>https://footwearnews.com/2020/shop/socks/corgi-butt-socks-amazon-1202904625/</link>
					<amzn:heroImage>https://pmcfootwearnews.files.wordpress.com/2020/01/corgi-socks.jpg</amzn:heroImage>
							<amzn:heroImageCaption>Amazon</amzn:heroImageCaption>
					<amzn:indexContent>False</amzn:indexContent>
		<amzn:products>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B079RMTPVJ/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Socksmith Corgi Butt Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[These socks come in several colors to choose from to suit different preferences.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Top Pick]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B072WK7ZCT/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[ModSocks Corgi Butt Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[These adorable socks are sure to garner attention and compliments wherever you show them off.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Honorable Mention]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07P98LKS6/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[HappyPop Corgi Butt Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Not only do these socks feature sweet corgi drawings but they also contain a cheeky message.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Also Consider]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
				</amzn:products>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If you love corgis, you&#8217;re not alone. In fact, Queen Elizabeth II is known for her long-time fondness of the breed and has reportedly had over 30 Pembroke Welsh Corgi dogs since she was young. Whether for you or a fellow corgi-loving friend, a pair of socks featuring those adorably furry critters makes a great addition to any sock drawer. <span style="font-family:-apple-system, BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen-Sans, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;">With this in mind, we rounded up some of our favorite styles for women featuring playful corgi butt prints. Each cotton-blend style comes in various colors for more buying options. </span></p>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B079RMTPVJ/" />
	</div>
	<p>This style features a Y-stitch heel, which forms a cup around the heel for added comfort and helps prevent the socks from fall down and bunching inside your shoe.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>These come in navy blue, gray and hot pink. The print includes two different colored corgis.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>The elastic band at the top may feel slightly tight for some.<strong></strong></p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B072WK7ZCT/" />
	</div>
	<p>These black crew socks show corgis in several positions and should fit women's shoe size 6-10.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>The toes and heels are reinforced for durability.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>They tend to run a little big.</p>
<p><strong></strong></p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07P98LKS6/" />
	</div>
	<p>These pink and blue socks feature cartoon-like corgi images with the playful phrase: "Guess what? Corgi butt."</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>They should comfortably fit a women's shoe size 6-12.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> These may be somewhat small.</p>
<p><strong></strong></p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Best Foot Massagers for Pampering Your Feet</title>
		<author>Charlie Carballo</author>		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 20:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<link>https://footwearnews.com/2019/shop/health/top-foot-massager-miko-shiatsu-spa-electric-manual-amazon-1202807567/</link>
					<amzn:heroImage>https://pmcfootwearnews.files.wordpress.com/2019/07/nekteck-foot-massager.jpg</amzn:heroImage>
							<amzn:heroImageCaption>Amazon</amzn:heroImageCaption>
					<amzn:indexContent>False</amzn:indexContent>
		<amzn:products>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B01H5QZ5X8/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Miko Shiatsu Foot Massager]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Miko’s shiatsu foot massager is a multifunctional, pampering product equipped with various pressure settings and sensations.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Overall]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B00SMJIYNG/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[TheraFlow Dual Foot Massager Roller]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Be your own reflexologist with this manual foot massager that puts all the control in your own hands — and feet.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Manual Design]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07G43L5QP/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Snailax Shiatsu Foot Massager]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Snailax’s heated massager provides all-over relief for the most tired feet.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Heated Foot Massager]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B0143X748U/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Belmint Shiatsu Foot Massager]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Belmint’s massager works to relax even the tightest of muscles.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Shiatsu Foot Massager]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B06WGP2CVL/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Nekteck Foot Massager]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Adjust the height of Nekteck’s foot massager for effective use anywhere you put it.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Under the Desk Foot Massager]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07F2H1NQR/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Renpho Shiatsu Foot Massager]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Customize the heat, pressure, timing and more with Renpho’s heated foot massager.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Most Settings]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B074P2M8N8/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[CloudMassage Foot Massage Machine]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Target your feet and calves with this massager.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Most Versatile]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
				</amzn:products>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Your feet deserve some TLC. Whether it&#8217;s hours spent standing, working out or being exposed to the elements, pampering your piggies with a foot massage can help enhance your overall mood. What&#8217;s more, a foot massager can lead to better sleep since it increases blood circulation. Daily kneading around the feet can help relieve stiffness around the ankle, too. Sessions at spas can absorb a lot of money and time, but there are several foot massage devices on the market that share the same benefits, all from the comfort of your own home. Here, we&#8217;ve selected some of the best options that will make you want to incorporate foot massages into your daily routine, from mildly intense foot relief to powerful electronic styles ideal for people who suffer from more severe pain.</p>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B01H5QZ5X8/" />
	</div>
	<p>Who says you can't have it all? This style incorporates heat and air pressure with deep kneading, vibrating and rolling settings. The foot massager also has five pressure settings that can be adjusted remotely for those who want either a firm or light touch.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> The device can be used with or without socks. Some of the programmable techniques can help provide relief from a variety of foot care woes, including plantar fasciitis, chronic pain, muscle tension and more. The slip-in massager covers the entire foot and is designed with two chambers that apply pressure on the bottom and sides. Plus, it comes with a no-risk warranty for a year.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> For those who have sensitive feet, it's recommended that you begin with socks for short 15-minute daily sessions until you're ready to increase the pressure.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B00SMJIYNG/" />
	</div>
	<p>This manual roller by TheraFlow takes a traditional approach with wooden construction inspired by ancient foot reflexology techniques, along with a modern design that's so lightweight it can be used anywhere.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> It's made of sturdy theaceae wood with gripping pads under the base, so there's no worry about the massager slipping while you're maneuvering your feet. The device incorporates 10 independently moving rollers that cannot compare to some of its battery-operated or plug-in counterparts on the market. The massager comes with a satisfaction-guaranteed policy, so if you're unhappy you can get a replacement or a refund with no questions asked.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> The device can be squeaky to some users, so adjust the pressure you apply accordingly.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07G43L5QP/" />
	</div>
	<p>Snailax's product has shiatsu foot massager with optional heat function and easy-to-use detachable and washable feet sleeves for clean care.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>This device offers rolling, air compression and heating functions to give you a deep kneading massage with three auto massage modes. It offers a double air compression massage for your instep and ankles thanks to two integrated airbags. The foot sleeves are removable and washable.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> It automatically stops after 15 minutes.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B0143X748U/" />
	</div>
	<p>Coming in a sleek metallic silver colorway, Belmint's foot massager, with its deep-kneading Shiatsu techniques, is a great addition to any home.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> This product is a strong foot massager with air pressure maxing out a 50 kPa which, according to Belmint, is 20% stronger than most other brands. This heating massager provides active compression that creates a pumping action to the front of your feet.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>This massages mostly the front of the foot, more than the heel and backside of the foot.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B06WGP2CVL/" />
	</div>
	<p>Nekeck's massager is equipped with six massage heads with 18 rotating massage nodes for widespread pressure.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> This soothing, heating massager adjusts to three levels of height so you can use it in any setting from sitting on the couch to under your desk at the office.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> It only massages the bottom of the feet.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07F2H1NQR/" />
	</div>
	<p>Renpho's foot massager comes in two models: one that's touch controlled and another that's remote-controlled. Both include rotation balls, a rolling stick, a heating function and compression.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> With three kneading intensities and three pressure levels, this massager can be modified to your preference and settings along with an added heating function to help increase the circulation in your feet. The massage can also be set for 15- or 30-minute sessions. It features a nonslip rubber pad underneath the unit to prevent slippage. The cloth cover on the inside of the unit is machine-washable for easy maintenance.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> It only fits up to a men's size 12.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B074P2M8N8/" />
	</div>
	<p>This massager can be used on your feet, your calves or your ankles for all-over relief. Its dual-channel design creates a comfortable base for settling your legs.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> CloudMassage provides an electric foot massager with a deep kneading shiatsu technique that features multiple settings for heat, air compression pressure and vibration.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> There is no remote control, so it may be difficult to turn on if laying on your stomach.</p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>These Animal Paw Socks Are Perfect for Halloween, Cosplay and More</title>
		<author>Allie Fasanella</author>		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 19:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<link>https://footwearnews.com/2020/shop/socks/these-animal-paw-socks-are-perfect-for-halloween-cosplay-and-more-1202904463/</link>
					<amzn:heroImage>https://pmcfootwearnews.files.wordpress.com/2020/01/untitled-13.jpg</amzn:heroImage>
							<amzn:heroImageCaption>Amazon</amzn:heroImageCaption>
					<amzn:indexContent>False</amzn:indexContent>
		<amzn:products>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B078ZBVRC2/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Tiaronics Animal Paws Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[This brand gives you a wide variety of options to choose from.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Top Pick]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07KLQBS35/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[FreeNFond Animal Paw Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Channel a polar bear, dinosaur and more in these socks.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Honorable Mention]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07KWXTHS9/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Cosweet Animal Paw Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[These are offered in adult and kids sizes so everyone can join in on the fun.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Bang for Your Buck]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
				</amzn:products>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Socks with 3D printed animal paw designs are meant to look realistic, making them a great pick for completing Halloween costumes and cosplay outfits. They also make fun novelty gifts for kids and animal-loving adults. With this in mind, we took it upon ourselves to curate a list of some of the best animal paw socks on the market for men, women and children. Each pick is offered in a range of animal-themed options to choose from and is made with soft cotton and breathable polyester for a comfortable fit.</p>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B078ZBVRC2/" />
	</div>
	<p>These socks are offered in over 10 animal themes to choose from, including dogs, cats, zebra and tigers.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>They're designed to comfortably fit most feet up to men's size 13.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>Some may find them a little thin.</p>
<p><strong></strong></p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07KLQBS35/" />
	</div>
	<p>This style is available in seven options inspired by creatures like a polar bear, eager and even dinosaur.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>They're also designed to fit feet up to a men's size 13 foot. These come with a one-year money-back guarantee if you're not satisfied with your purchase.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>They may also be on the smaller side.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07KWXTHS9/" />
	</div>
	<p>These crew socks come in a pack with three different animal paw styles: tiger, cat and leopard.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>They're available in adult and kids sizes.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>They may run small.</p>
<p><strong></strong></p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Best Compression Socks</title>
		<author>Samantha Peters</author>		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 19:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<link>https://footwearnews.com/2019/shop/socks/best-compression-socks-amazon-1202772796/</link>
					<amzn:heroImage>https://pmcfootwearnews.files.wordpress.com/2019/04/best-compression-socks.jpg</amzn:heroImage>
							<amzn:heroImageCaption>Shutterstock/sportpoint</amzn:heroImageCaption>
					<amzn:indexContent>False</amzn:indexContent>
		<amzn:products>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B01J4MF5UY/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Physix Gear Compression Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Physix Gear’s compression socks are meant to improve lower leg circulation.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Top Pick]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07GBYZL7R/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Charmking Compression Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Change up your style every day in Charmking’s fun patterns.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Pattern Variety]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07G2SLW1P/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[SB SOX Compression Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[SB SOX’s anti-static compression socks make for easy wear under clothing.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best for Moisture Management]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B071ZZBZRD/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Iseasoo Knee-High Compression Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Iseasoo’s specialized fibers are designed to reduce pain.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best for Odor Control]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B013XL3Z6I/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Go2Socks Compression Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Reduce swelling and numbness in these medical-grade compression socks.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Also Consider]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B01N6N3DXV/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Laite Hebe Compression Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Target varicose veins in Laite Hebe’s compression socks.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Also Consider]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B01MQW3JK6/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Thirty48 Compression Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Find relief from achy arches and heel pain in Thirty48’s compression sleeve.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best for Plantar Fasciitis]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
				</amzn:products>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Compression socks are often recommended for diabetics, pregnant women and other people with circulatory issues, but just about anyone can wear them, as long as they’re comfortable. They offer more pressure at the ankle than the calf to support blood flow in the legs, making them ideal as well for people who spend most of their day on their feet or traveling on planes. Most compression socks are made with a blend of synthetic fabrics that provide a snug yet stretchy fit and come in a range of lengths and firmness to fit any need or preference. To help you wade through all the options, we’ve rounded up some of the best unisex styles you can buy. Read on to shop for them all.</p>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B01J4MF5UY/" />
	</div>
	<p>Whether you're a runner, nurse or simply looking to improve lower leg circulation, these knee-high socks are a great pick since they wick away moisture.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>These socks offer compression for those seeking a high level of support (20-30 mmHg). Constructed of a breathable nylon and spandex blend, they don’t lose compression after washing, include stay-put cuffs that don’t roll down during wear and include shock-absorbing technology.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:  </strong>The elastic band at the top of the sock may be constricting and these may run large.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07GBYZL7R/" />
	</div>
	<p>For a slightly lower-grade compression sock (15–20 mmHg), this option offers sturdy support at an unbeatable price.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> These are available as a pack of seven or eight, so you won't have to worry about doing laundry so frequently. They are also available in plain and patterned options to suit any style and feature targeted compression zones that help relieve pain associated with plantar fasciitis; they also include up to 80% nylon for a breathable and flexible fit.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>Styles may shrink after washing.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07G2SLW1P/" />
	</div>
	<p>These socks from SB SOX include 20-30 mmHg of compression and are available in four sizes.</p>
<p><b>Pros: </b>They are made with a durable yet lightweight and breathable fabric for easy wear. They are also anti-static to stop the growth of bacteria and wick away sweat.</p>
<p><b>Cons: </b>The toe is not seamless.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B071ZZBZRD/" />
	</div>
	<p>With a lower setting of 15-20 mmHg compression, Iseasoo's socks are perfect for anyone looking for a not-too-tight feel.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> This set comes with eight different pairs so you'll never be without one; the fabric is anti-itch to reduce irritation and features copper, which is antimicrobial and helps keep foul odors at bay.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>These may fit tight on wide feet.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B013XL3Z6I/" />
	</div>
	<p>Go2Socks' compression socks have 20-30 mmHg of compression and are made with tough, high-quality fabrics.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> These socks are available in single or double pairs of fun patterns and are made to reduce swelling, circulatory issues and numbness. These allow you to manage your edema or DVT in comfort and style.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> The brand lets you know if your calf size is larger than the prescribed size. If it is, you will experience a tighter feel.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B01N6N3DXV/" />
	</div>
	<p>Laite Hebe's set of compression socks comes with eight pairs of soft yet tight compression socks.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>These socks are meant to provide muscle recovery and to target varicose veins. They have 360-degree stretch for all-day wear and special construction to enhance blood circulation.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> They only offered in two sizes.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B01MQW3JK6/" />
	</div>
	<p>These high level compression socks (20–30 mmHg) socks provide targeted pressure to the arch of your foot to increase blood flow, boost circulation and relieve inflammation for associated with plantar fasciitis. The stretchy and ultralightweight fabric is effective for a more minimalist feel.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> These compression sleeves provide compression to your foot and lower calf while still allowing free movement in the toes.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> If you want calf compression, these sleeves aren't for you.</p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>These Moisturizing Socks Will Save Super-Dry Feet</title>
		<author>Allie Fasanella</author>		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 21:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<link>https://footwearnews.com/2020/shop/socks/best-moisturizing-socks-1202903748/</link>
					<amzn:heroImage>https://pmcfootwearnews.files.wordpress.com/2020/01/silkease-moisturizing-socks.jpg</amzn:heroImage>
							<amzn:heroImageCaption>Amazon</amzn:heroImageCaption>
					<amzn:indexContent>False</amzn:indexContent>
		<amzn:products>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B00O81S77A/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[NatraCure Gel Moisturizing Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[These socks target dry cuticles as well as cracked heels and rough skin.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Moisturizing Sock]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B06XS48TXH/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Codream Moisturizing Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[These Codream socks are designed to deliver softer feet in no time.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Moisturizing Heel Sleeve]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07VDP84KZ/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[CareMe+ SILKEase Moisturizing Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[These CareMe+ SilkEase socks are properly ventilated and made with breathable cotton.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Honorable Mention Heel Sleeve]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
				</amzn:products>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If you suffer from dry, cracked skin on your feet, chances are, a pair of moisturizing socks will be a total lifesaver. They typically feature a blend of soothing essential oils, vitamins and gels that help replenish the skin and prevent moisture loss. To ensure you find the best ones on the market, we gathered some of our favorite moisturizing socks for men and women. We included two heel-sleeves that are specifically designed to target callused heels and a pair of toe socks to nourish the whole foot, even in between the toes.</p>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B00O81S77A/" />
	</div>
	<p>These vibrant toe socks feature a SmartGel inner lining that slowly releases a mineral oil containing shea butter, vitamin E, aloe vera and vitamin F forte.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>Each toe is enclosed with SmartGel to treat dry cuticles. They come in three sizes to choose from.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>They might feel long for some.</p>
<p><strong></strong></p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B06XS48TXH/" />
	</div>
	<p>These no-toe socks have a gel lining and feature a cotton-spandex blend for ultimate stretchy, form-fitting comfort. They're infused with vitamin E, olive oil, grapeseed oil, jojoba oil and rose oil.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>Vented holes allow for breathability. An interior silicone heel pad keeps the lotion where it belongs to effectively treat the heel. These come as a pack of two.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>If you want to treat the entire foot, these sleeves aren't for you.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07VDP84KZ/" />
	</div>
	<p>These 100% cotton toeless socks have gel in the heel and are infused with olive, jojoba and grapeseed oil.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>They're designed with ventilation to help keep feet cool and fresh. Lavender and rose essential oil offer a soothing scent. They come as a pack of three.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>The heel may become somewhat discolored after several wears and washes.<strong></strong></p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Best Roll-Top Cotton Socks for a Comfortable Fit</title>
		<author>Allie Fasanella</author>		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 20:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<link>https://footwearnews.com/2020/shop/socks/roll-top-cotton-socks-women-amazon-1202903700/</link>
					<amzn:heroImage>https://pmcfootwearnews.files.wordpress.com/2020/01/roll-top-socks.jpg</amzn:heroImage>
							<amzn:heroImageCaption>Amazon</amzn:heroImageCaption>
					<amzn:indexContent>False</amzn:indexContent>
		<amzn:products>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B075S57SQC/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[HUE Roll Top Shortie Sock]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[These roll-top socks are built for long-lasting comfort.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Top Pick]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B01D3JI092/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[K. Bell Roll Top Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[These K. Bell socks are designed to fit most women’s shoe sizes.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Honorable Mention]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B00UXD5NWY/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[StyleGaga Roll Top Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[These crew socks are offered in a wide variety of neutral and vibrant colors to choose from.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Bang for Your Buck]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
				</amzn:products>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If you have bigger calves or simply struggle to find elastic-top socks that don&#8217;t feel constricting, roll-top socks might be your answer. A good pair should be soft and somewhat breathable for optimal comfort. With this in mind, we went on the hunt for some of the best roll-top socks on the market for women. We ended up choosing several crew-length styles, all which are made with soft cotton and come in several colors. Each option also features a touch of spandex to help keep the socks upright while you wear them.</p>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B075S57SQC/" />
	</div>
	<p>In addition to cotton, these socks contain 34% nylon and 2% spandex, which makes them stronger and stretchier.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>They're offered in black, gray and brown. These come as a pack of three.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>They may be small for some.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B01D3JI092/" />
	</div>
	<p>These socks feature 28% nylon and 2% spandex, delivering added durability and a better fit.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>These are available in eight color variations to choose from.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>Some may find them a tad thin.</p>
<p><strong></strong></p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B00UXD5NWY/" />
	</div>
	<p>These socks are made with 65% cotton and 35% spandex for soft, breathable, foot-contouring comfort.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>You can choose from a five-pack of either black, gray or white or get six pairs in all different colors.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> Some may find them to be slightly tight.<strong></strong></p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cushioned No-Show Socks That Stay Put</title>
		<author>Allie Fasanella</author>		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 19:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<link>https://footwearnews.com/2020/shop/socks/cushioned-cotton-no-show-socks-amazon-1202903648/</link>
					<amzn:heroImage>https://pmcfootwearnews.files.wordpress.com/2020/01/no-show-socks.jpg</amzn:heroImage>
							<amzn:heroImageCaption>Amazon</amzn:heroImageCaption>
					<amzn:indexContent>False</amzn:indexContent>
		<amzn:products>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B010RSE4GA/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Nike Cushion No Show Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[These Nike Performance socks provide ample cushioning underfoot for superior impact absorption.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Top Pick]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B00E4I4XV6/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Hanes Cushion No-Show Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[These socks from Hanes are designed to prevent unwanted odors.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Honorable Mention]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07JZTF9R5/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Pro Mountain No-Show Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[These Pro Mountain socks are specifically engineered to prevent heel slippage.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Also Consider]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
				</amzn:products>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A good pair of comfortable no-show socks can be hard to get your hands on. They so often slip off the heel and end up bunched up in your shoe, which only leads to discomfort. Nobody wants to be constantly reaching down to adjust their socks, so to help you find some of the best styles on the market, we rounded up some of our favorite options for men and women. From brands like Nike and Hanes, these styles feature a soft fabric blend of mostly cotton with cushioned soles that reduce impact and improve their overall comfort.</p>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B010RSE4GA/" />
	</div>
	<p>These Nike socks have a thick, comfort-enhancing terry sole that absorbs impact and a ribbed arch band that wraps your midfoot for a supportive feel.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>Dri-FIT technology helps keep your feet dry and comfortable. These packs of six pairs come in three colors and two sizes. <strong><br />
</strong></p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>Some may find they fit slightly large.<strong></strong></p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B00E4I4XV6/" />
	</div>
	<p>These Hanes socks feature extra-thick, impact-absorbing cushioning underfoot.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> Fresh IQ advanced odor-protection technology attacks odor-causing bacteria. They're offered in black and white, and they come as a pack of six.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>The fabric may shed a bit.</p>
<p><strong></strong></p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07JZTF9R5/" />
	</div>
	<p>These no show socks feature 73% combed cotton and 20% spandex for a foot-hugging fit.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>They're available in multiple sizes and colors, and they all come in packs of eight pairs. A mesh construction on the instep allows for optimal airflow. A 3D Y heel stitch and silicone pad ensures they're slip-proof.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>These may be somewhat small.</p>
<p><strong></strong></p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>These Men&#8217;s Ankle Socks Have Thick Cushioning for Ultimate Comfort</title>
		<author>Allie Fasanella</author>		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 17:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<link>https://footwearnews.com/2020/shop/socks/best-cushioned-ankle-socks-mens-1202903535/</link>
					<amzn:heroImage>https://pmcfootwearnews.files.wordpress.com/2020/01/carhartt-.jpg</amzn:heroImage>
							<amzn:heroImageCaption>Amazon</amzn:heroImageCaption>
					<amzn:indexContent>False</amzn:indexContent>
		<amzn:products>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07LFYM6BZ/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Cooplus Ankle Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[These socks are breathable and won’t slip off your heel.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Top Pick]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B01GIIX4K0/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Carhartt Force Work Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[These socks have moisture-wicking capabilities so your feet stay dry and fresh.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Honorable Mention]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B01FRBTOUS/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Hanes Max Cushion Ankle Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[These Hanes socks are soft and durable, and they fight odors.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Bang for Your Buck]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
				</amzn:products>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If you&#8217;ve been struggling to find ankle socks with ample cushioning underfoot, you&#8217;re in luck. To help narrow down the wide range of options on the market, we took it upon ourselves to curate a brief list of our favorite styles for men. We pulled styles from well-respected brands like Hanes, Carhartt and more for you to choose from. Each low-cut style is made with lightweight, durable, fast-drying polyester and spandex for elasticity. They all feature push cushioning with reinforced toes and heels for added durability and comfort.</p>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07LFYM6BZ/" />
	</div>
	<p>These ankle socks feature mesh ventilation to regulate foot temperature and elastic in the arch for support and stability. Cushioning underfoot protects against impact.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>An ergonomic 3D Y heel design and heel tab help prevent the socks from slipping down. They come in black, gray and white.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>Some may find them a bit small.</p>
<p><strong></strong></p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B01GIIX4K0/" />
	</div>
	<p>These Carhartt socks have FastDry technology, which moves sweat away from the skin.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>Racetrack mesh ventilation channels cool feet, while antimicrobial technology resists tough odors. Built-in arch support prevents the sock from bunching. They come in 2 sizes and 2 colors. They come as a pack of three.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>Some may find they run big.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B01FRBTOUS/" />
	</div>
	<p>These Hanes socks feature a ComfortBlend fabric combination of soft, breathable cotton, durable polyester and spandex.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>FreshIQ advanced odor-protection technology attacks odor-causing bacteria to help you feel fresh all day. They're offered in black and white. These come as a pack of six.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>They may be a tad snug for some wearers. </p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Show Off Your Best Side in These Custom Face Socks</title>
		<author>Claudia Miller</author>		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 15:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<link>https://footwearnews.com/2020/shop/socks/top-custom-face-socks-1202903246/</link>
					<amzn:heroImage>https://pmcfootwearnews.files.wordpress.com/2020/01/my-pup-socks-custom-face.jpg</amzn:heroImage>
							<amzn:heroImageCaption>Amazon</amzn:heroImageCaption>
					<amzn:indexContent>False</amzn:indexContent>
		<amzn:products>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07SGXDFTN/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[MyPupSocks Custom Face Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Wear a face on your feet in these customizable socks.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Top Pick]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07KPFPP53/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[D-Story Custom Face Soft Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Choose from different colors and cute phrases with D-Story’s customizable socks.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Honorable Mention]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07SVCQLT3/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[AnnHomeArt Custom Photo Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Include the whole family in AnnHomeArt’s face-printed socks.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best for Group Pictures]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
				</amzn:products>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Looking for a fun gag gift or an easy way to show your love and appreciation for someone? If so, we have the perfect idea for you: Custom face socks. These pairs are screen printed with your choice of image — whether it&#8217;s your best friend, celebrity crush or your favorite pet — for a fun and eclectic twist to your sock drawer. You can also put your own face on them for a hysterical present that a loved one won&#8217;t forget. Shop our favorite pairs from D-Story, MyPupSocks and more that all feature individualized designs and unique detailing.</p>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07SGXDFTN/" />
	</div>
	<p>MyPupSocks provides customizable socks made from high-quality polyester.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> These socks feature mini printed heads of the image you uploaded for a humourous, unbeatable set.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> These can't be tumbled dry because it could affect the coloring.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07KPFPP53/" />
	</div>
	<p>D-Story's polyester socks feature a cap toe and heel design with customizable patterns.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> In addition to adding your image of choice, you can also opt for styles that include phrases like "I Heart Mom" or "I Heart Dad" for a fun twist.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> This is one size fits most unisex sock.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07SVCQLT3/" />
	</div>
	<p>AnnHomeArt's polyester socks feature stacked images of your choice.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> Upload your photo to create a customizable design that can feature one face or many, making a great way to celebrate the whole family.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> Customizing and shipping may take extended time since these are made by order.</p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Make a Statement in These Funky Animal-Themed Dress Socks for Men</title>
		<author>Claudia Miller</author>		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 15:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<link>https://footwearnews.com/2020/shop/socks/novelty-dress-socks-men-1202903245/</link>
					<amzn:heroImage>https://pmcfootwearnews.files.wordpress.com/2020/01/cotton-idea-socks.jpg</amzn:heroImage>
							<amzn:heroImageCaption>Amazon</amzn:heroImageCaption>
					<amzn:indexContent>False</amzn:indexContent>
		<amzn:products>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B075H7VYQQ/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[WeciBor Dress Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[From rhinos to corgis, you’ll never run out of fun options with WeciBor’s socks.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Bulk Set]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07D93BPTV/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Socks n Socks Novelty Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Change up your normal socks with these wild designs.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Honorable Mention]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07DD9L94D/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Cotton Idea Animal Pattern Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Channel your favorite jungle animal with these striped and dotted socks.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Animal-Print Socks]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
				</amzn:products>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In more formal office settings, it can be hard to deviate from the standard suit-and-tie dress code. For a subtle a pop of personality that won&#8217;t get you called into HR, add a pair of animal-themed socks to your look. No matter your critter preference, we brought you some of our favorite pairs featuring a range of furry creatures, from corgis and other pup breeds to more comical designs like a panda in suspenders (talk about a good conversation starter!). Every pair is budget-friendly, too, so we wouldn&#8217;t blame you if you go hog wild and purchase multiple pairs.</p>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B075H7VYQQ/" />
	</div>
	<p>WeciBor cotton dress socks come in various colorways and designs.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> This set of 12 socks features animals ranging from rhinoceroses to corgis and to patterns like Pacman and cameras so that you can wear a different pair for every occasion.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> These may fit small on feet larger than size 10.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07D93BPTV/" />
	</div>
	<p>This Socks n Socks set has four pairs with solid-colored banded tops.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>Impress your coworkers in one of these four pairs that include a panda in a suit and walking penguins.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> These may be thinner than expected.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07DD9L94D/" />
	</div>
	<p>Cotton Idea provides a package of five socks made from super-soft Turkish cotton.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> These socks feature animal-print designs like cheetah and cow print for an on-trend look.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> These may slip down on thinner calves.</p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Cutest Knee-High Animal Socks for Girls</title>
		<author>Claudia Miller</author>		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 15:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<link>https://footwearnews.com/2020/shop/socks/best-knee-high-animal-socks-1202903244/</link>
					<amzn:heroImage>https://pmcfootwearnews.files.wordpress.com/2020/01/color-city-socks.jpg</amzn:heroImage>
							<amzn:heroImageCaption>Amazon</amzn:heroImageCaption>
					<amzn:indexContent>False</amzn:indexContent>
		<amzn:products>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B01MG7GY1E/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Color City Knee-High Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Sport socks with your favorite dog breeds thanks to Color City.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best for Dog Lovers]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B01JI1QG04/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Gellwhu Knee High Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Another adorable option, these feature ear-like accents at the hem.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Wide Variety]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07P12Z1R8/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Cismark Cartoon Animal Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[From penguins to unicorns, Cismark has wild animal socks for you.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Also Consider]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
				</amzn:products>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Whether she&#8217;s dressing up for crazy sock day at school or looking to switch up her everyday gear, your teen or preteen can always reach for a pair of animal-themed socks. Even better if they hit the knee for a bold look. The options we&#8217;ve curated are adorned with various critters, including cats, dogs and even sparkling unicorns. Plus, they come in tons of bright colors. Not sure how to style them? These sets will look great with a pleated skirt and a plain T-shirt for an attention-drawing ensemble or over leggings for an &#8217;80s-inspired look.</p>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B01MG7GY1E/" />
	</div>
	<p>Color City's knee-high socks feature a cotton-spandex band and elastic top band for a secure fit.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> These socks include various pooch breeds like schnauzers, chihuahuas and bulldogs. They fit girls ages 3 to 12.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> These may fit short on taller frames.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B01JI1QG04/" />
	</div>
	<p>Gellwhu's cotton-blend socks come in a pack of eight different colorways and prints.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> These socks feature added ears for a cartoon-like effect on each animal, including like cats, raccoons and bears.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> These socks may fit like knee-high socks or over-the-knee socks, depending on the height of the girl.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07P12Z1R8/" />
	</div>
	<p>With enhanced hold cuffs, the Cismark cotton socks in each six pack are lightweight and breathable.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> These socks include animals like unicorns, giraffes, penguins and more in a fantastical, fun style.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> These run small.</p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>These Fuzzy Animal Socks Are Perfect for Pet Lovers</title>
		<author>Claudia Miller</author>		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 14:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<link>https://footwearnews.com/2020/shop/socks/best-fuzzy-animal-socks-1202903239/</link>
					<amzn:heroImage>https://pmcfootwearnews.files.wordpress.com/2020/01/loritta-socks.jpg</amzn:heroImage>
							<amzn:heroImageCaption>Amazon</amzn:heroImageCaption>
					<amzn:indexContent>False</amzn:indexContent>
		<amzn:products>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B0784DNR55/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Loritta Fuzzy Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Show some animal love in Loritta’s soft socks.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Top Pick]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07YXKHG4C/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Zmart Fuzzy Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Add of pop of color in Zmart’s fuzzy socks.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Bang for Your Buck]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07GNFBT36/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Ysense Fuzzy Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Pick from a wide variety of animal-inspired socks in this set.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Variety]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
				</amzn:products>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There&#8217;s no better feeling than kicking off your shoes after a long day of work and throwing on your favorite pair of fuzzy socks. These fun, fluffy socks come in a variety of colors and styles, but for you animal lovers, we may just have found your dream pairs. These women&#8217;s styles feature cats, dogs and even less domestic creatures like lions for a fun addition to your look while lounging around at home. They&#8217;re all made from comfy, soft fabric to keep your feet super cozy.</p>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B0784DNR55/" />
	</div>
	<p>Loritta's socks are made from soft microfiber with elasticized top bands to help them stay up.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> This three-pack includes different pairs of animal-inspired socks, including cats and dogs.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> These may be slippery on smoother floors.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07YXKHG4C/" />
	</div>
	<p>This cozy four-pack is a great deal.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> The fun animal-inspired socks should be somewhat breathable and stretchy thanks to their blend of combed cotton and spandex. Styles include a pig, fox, wolf, bear and more.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> The brand advises that these socks may shrink if dried at a high temperature.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07GNFBT36/" />
	</div>
	<p>Ysense's set of three socks are made with a blend of polyester and spandex for a comfy fit.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>These socks include animals like cats, squirrels, zebras and more for a variety that will always keep you entertained and warm.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>These socks may not stay up as well on smaller calves.</p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lacy Fishnet Thigh-High Stockings That Won&#8217;t Fall Down</title>
		<author>Allie Fasanella</author>		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 23:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<link>https://footwearnews.com/2020/shop/womens/best-lace-top-fishnet-thigh-highs-1202903109/</link>
					<amzn:heroImage>https://pmcfootwearnews.files.wordpress.com/2020/01/mila-marutti.jpg</amzn:heroImage>
							<amzn:heroImageCaption>Amazon</amzn:heroImageCaption>
					<amzn:indexContent>False</amzn:indexContent>
		<amzn:products>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07QLYBQF7/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Joyaria Fishnets]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[These fishnet thigh-high stockings should be comfortable, durable and stay in place.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Top Choice]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B000GISJRC/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Leg Avenue Fishnets]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[These Leg Avenue fishnets are ultra stretchy for easy on and off.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Honorable Mention]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07K5JP74X/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Mila Marutti Fishnets]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[These fishnets come in a plethora of sizes and colors to choose from.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Color &amp; Size Options]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
				</amzn:products>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Thigh-high fishnet stockings are already attention-grabbing, but when you add a lace-top detail, you&#8217;re sure to stand out. When looking for comfortable over-the-knee stockings, you should consider their elasticity and durability since you don&#8217;t want them to be too constricting or fall apart after just a few wears. And if you&#8217;d rather have them with an attached garter belt, a good pair should feature sticky silicone at the top to help keep them up. Here, we came up with a list of some of the best fishnet thigh-high stockings with lacy details for you to consider. Each style is available in a variety of colors to suit different preferences.</p>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07QLYBQF7/" />
	</div>
	<p>These thigh-highs are made of 80% nylon and 20% spandex, delivering a softy, stretchy fit.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>They come in multiple sizes, several colors and a pack of one or two. The lace top features a soft double silicone band designed to maintain its tension, stickiness and elasticity over time.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>They may run somewhat small.</p>
<p><strong></strong></p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B000GISJRC/" />
	</div>
	<p>This style is made of 100% spandex and also features a silicone band lace top.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>They're offered in black, burgundy, red and white.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>Some may find them a little tight.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07K5JP74X/" />
	</div>
	<p>These silky fishnet thigh-highs have a silicone stay-up strip and are offered in five sizes, from small to XL.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>They come in sky blue, violet, light pink, classic black, white, tan, gray and red. You can also choose whether you'd like a back seam detail or not. They're available with small and large netting.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>Some may find them a tad itchy.</p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Restore Cracked Heels in These Moisturizing Socks</title>
		<author>Claudia Miller</author>		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<link>https://footwearnews.com/2020/shop/socks/best-moisturizing-socks-dry-feet-1202902572/</link>
					<amzn:heroImage>https://pmcfootwearnews.files.wordpress.com/2020/01/codream-socks.jpg</amzn:heroImage>
							<amzn:heroImageCaption>Amazon</amzn:heroImageCaption>
					<amzn:indexContent>False</amzn:indexContent>
		<amzn:products>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B00O81S77A/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[NatraCure Gel Moisturizing Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Restore cracked heels in NatraCure’s gel-lined socks.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Moisturizing Toe Socks]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B01N7SR6XB/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Codream Moisturizing Gel Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Encase dry feet in soothing moisture thanks to Codream’s socks.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Moisturizing Ankle Socks]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B075JN1HPQ/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[ZenToes Moisturizing Heel Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Target cracked heels in these special sleeves.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Moisturizing Heel Socks]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
				</amzn:products>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Whether it&#8217;s boot or sandal season, feet undergo quite a bit of wear and tear. If you suffer from dry, cracked heels as a result, it may be time to treat them to some moisturizing socks. These pairs are designed to replenish even the driest and most damaged skin, infused with essential oils, vitamins and minerals for restoring feet to their original suppleness. Plus, they&#8217;re all gel-lined to also soften feet and provide a squishy feel. From classic ankle-sock styles to toe socks and sleeves made to target tough calluses, this list of styles we found includes an option to cater to every need.</p>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B00O81S77A/" />
	</div>
	<p>NatraCure's socks wrap your foot in soft fabric and are made to hydrate feet to relieve cracked, dry skin with essential oils.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>These socks are made with the brand's SmartGel technology that slowly releases botanical oils, aloe vera and vitamins over time for continuous effects.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>The brand states that the inner gel lining at first will feel dry and rubbery against your skin before warming to the temperature of your body.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B01N7SR6XB/" />
	</div>
	<p>This two-pack of socks from Codream has a fuzzy fabric exterior that is washable and reusable.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> The gel lining of these socks uses Vitamin E and mineral oils including jojoba oil, grape seed oil and olive oil to provide moisture to callused heels.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> The brand recommends s<span class="a-list-item">oaking your feet in warm water and w</span><span class="a-list-item">aiting until your dry skin has softened before putting these on.</span></p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B075JN1HPQ/" />
	</div>
	<p>ZenToes' flexible cotton-blend sleeves are designed to target cracked heels while letting toes breathe with two pairs per package.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> These toe-less socks are ideal for warmer weather and can be worn on their own or with sandals and flip-flops; they are gel-lined to relieve dry skin and work best when combined with other moisturizers and lotions too.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> These are one size fits all and unisex so they may fit every foot differently.</p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Men&#8217;s Padded Socks Help Relieve Foot Pain</title>
		<author>Allie Fasanella</author>		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<link>https://footwearnews.com/2020/shop/socks/best-padded-socks-foot-pain-1202903060/</link>
					<amzn:heroImage>https://pmcfootwearnews.files.wordpress.com/2020/01/dickies-mens-3-pack-heavyweight-cushion-compression-work-crew-socks.jpg</amzn:heroImage>
							<amzn:heroImageCaption>Amazon</amzn:heroImageCaption>
					<amzn:indexContent>False</amzn:indexContent>
		<amzn:products>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B00KLMEPXK/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Dickies Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[These Dickies socks are equipped to deliver top-notch compression and support for a superior fit.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Top Choice]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B005FYNXBY/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Fruit of the Loom]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[These Fruit of the Loom socks are not only plush, but made to keep feet dry and fresh.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Bang for Your Buck]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07K77BN6M/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Petrala Hiking Socks - 5 Pack]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[These hiking socks are engineered for breathable, cushioned comfort.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Hiking Style Sock]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
				</amzn:products>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If you&#8217;re someone who spends a lot of time on their feet, you know the importance of a good pair of well-cushioned socks. Thick padding throughout can make all the difference when you&#8217;ve been up and about for hours. With a wide variety of padded sock options on the market though, we decided to help narrow things down. We pulled styles for hiking and everyday wear from respected brands like Dickies and Fruit of the Loom. Each of our picks is made to be soft and stay up comfortably. They also come in a multipack so you get more than just a single pair.</p>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B00KLMEPXK/" />
	</div>
	<p>These Dickies socks are made with a breathable blend of plush cotton and polyester with a hint of spandex for added stretch.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>Impact areas are reinforced with heavier count yarns for improved durability. An Achilles heel protective pad provides cushioned comfort in high boots. Arch and ankle compression offer extra support and stability. They come in black, gray and white and as a pack of three.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>Some may find they run a bit big.</p>
<p><strong></strong></p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B005FYNXBY/" />
	</div>
	<p>These socks have a rugged, extra-thick cotton construction with a cushioned foot and reinforced sole.</p>
<p><strong style="font-family:-apple-system, BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen-Sans, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;">Pros: </strong>Ventilation channels and antimicrobial, moisture-wicking fibers keep socks dry, comfortable, and fresh. A spandex knitting provides a snug fit and retains shape even after repeated washings. They come in three colors and sizes to choose from and are available as a pack of six.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>They may be small for some.</p>
<p><strong></strong></p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07K77BN6M/" />
	</div>
	<p>These contain a blend of combed cotton, polyester, nylon and elastic for optimal comfort.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>Over 400 mesh holes allow your feet to breathe and keep them dry. They feature thick padding from toe to heel and thick stitching at the bottom for better grip on hardwood and tile floors.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> Some may wish they were slightly thicker.<strong></strong></p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>These Striped Socks and Tights Will Add a Fun Twist to Outfits</title>
		<author>Allie Fasanella</author>		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 20:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<link>https://footwearnews.com/2020/shop/womens/nylon-striped-stockings-socks-1202902991/</link>
					<amzn:heroImage>https://pmcfootwearnews.files.wordpress.com/2020/01/music-legs-pin-striped-pantyhose.jpg</amzn:heroImage>
							<amzn:heroImageCaption>Amazon</amzn:heroImageCaption>
					<amzn:indexContent>False</amzn:indexContent>
		<amzn:products>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B002M0EZ1G/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Leg Avenue Stockings]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[These thigh-high socks from Leg Avenue are suitable for a variety of occasions.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Over-the-Knee Socks]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B00O8M7P22/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Music Legs Pantyhose]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Complete with a pinstripe design, these sheer tights will spice up casual and formal dresses.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Wear-With-Everything Tights]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B079VSR632/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[ToBeInStyle Tights]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[These vibrant, playful tights are ideal for women of all body types.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Colorful Tights]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
				</amzn:products>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sporting a pair of striped socks or tights is an easy way to make a statement. Styles designed with straight-across horizontal stripes are often worn with costumes around Halloween or for cosplay. Meanwhile, if you&#8217;re hoping to make your legs look longer, you&#8217;ll want to choose stockings with vertical stripes. With this in mind, we curated a list of some of our favorite striped socks and tights on the market. We included a pair of over-the-knee socks and two full-length styles to suit different preferences. Each pick is made with abrasion-resistant nylon and designed to provide a flattering fit.</p>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B002M0EZ1G/" />
	</div>
	<p>These over-the-knee stockings with horizontal stripes feature a nylon-polyester construction.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>They come in 15 color combinations and multiple sizes to choose from.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>The elastic at the top may roll slightly.<strong></strong></p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B00O8M7P22/" />
	</div>
	<p>These vertical striped stockings are made with 88% nylon and 12% spandex.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>Their black and sheer pinstripe design naturally elongates the legs and can easily be dressed up or dressed down.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> Some may find they run easily.</p>
<p><strong></strong></p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B079VSR632/" />
	</div>
	<p>These nylon stockings also have horizontal stripes and come in three sizes.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>These are offered in 13 colorways.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>Some may find them a tad long.</p>
<p><strong></strong></p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Suspender Fishnet Stockings for Different Shapes and Sizes</title>
		<author>Allie Fasanella</author>		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 20:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<link>https://footwearnews.com/2020/shop/womens/best-suspender-fishnet-stockings-1202902929/</link>
					<amzn:heroImage>https://pmcfootwearnews.files.wordpress.com/2020/01/untitled-11.jpg</amzn:heroImage>
							<amzn:heroImageCaption>Amazon</amzn:heroImageCaption>
					<amzn:indexContent>False</amzn:indexContent>
		<amzn:products>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B0000YEC8C/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Leg Avenue Fishnet Suspender Hosiery]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[These Leg Avenue suspender hose are offered in multiple sizes to choose from.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Top Pick]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07NZ2YRG4/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Amuhou Fishnet Suspender Pantyhose]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[This value pack includes three pairs of sparkly rhinestone-embellished suspender pantyhose.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Bang for Your Buck]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07NW3VCPR/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Eralove Fishnet Suspender Pantyhose]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[This style is designed with plenty of stretch to fit a range of body types.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Also Consider]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
				</amzn:products>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Adding fishnet stockings to a look instantly adds some oomph. They&#8217;re edgy, and their construction makes them naturally more breathable than other styles without netting. And if you&#8217;re going for a thigh-high look but would rather not wear a garter belt, a pair of suspender pantyhose might be exactly what you need. In an effort to narrow down all the options on the market, we rounded up some of our favorite fishnet suspender stockings. We included a range of styles that are stretchy, durable and designed to fit different body shapes and sizes.</p>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B0000YEC8C/" />
	</div>
	<p>These fishnet suspenders are made with 100% polyester and have tight netting.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>They're available in regular and plus size.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>Some may find they run a tad small.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07NZ2YRG4/" />
	</div>
	<p>These chinlon-spandex stockings come in three designs and each features rhinestone detailing.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>They offer a 30-day money-back guarantee if you're not completely satisfied.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>The gems may begin to fall off after a while.<strong></strong></p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07NW3VCPR/" />
	</div>
	<p>These nylon-spandex-blend fishnets feature an intricate, eye-catching design down the front.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>Their elasticity ensures they accommodate a wide variety of sizes.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>They may be a little long for some.<strong></strong></p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>These Aloe-Infused Dress Socks Will Make Days Spent on Your Feet A Breeze</title>
		<author>Claudia Miller</author>		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 17:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<link>https://footwearnews.com/2020/shop/socks/best-aloe-infused-dress-socks-womens-1202902563/</link>
					<amzn:heroImage>https://pmcfootwearnews.files.wordpress.com/2020/01/obolvs-socks.jpg</amzn:heroImage>
							<amzn:heroImageCaption>Amazon</amzn:heroImageCaption>
					<amzn:indexContent>False</amzn:indexContent>
		<amzn:products>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B01J5BIFJW/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Enerwear Aloe-Infused Dress Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Find traction and durability in Enerwear’s dress socks.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Top Pick]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07V1LCTR1/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[oBolvs Dress Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[These socks help keep feet dry and offer a polished look.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best for Breathability]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07C3QX7J5/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[MediPeds Aloe Vera-Infused Roll Top Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Soothe your feet without restricting your calves in these roll-top socks.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Roll Top Style]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
				</amzn:products>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For anyone who has ever had a sunburn, you know the soothing properties of aloe vera, which is said to help alleviate irritation and even replenish dry skin. When infused into socks, the ingredient provides a great solution for soothing cracked heels. For long days on your feet at work, try these aloe-infused dress socks for women. Available in a range of versatile hues and classic crew-length silhouettes, they&#8217;re designed to be professional in appearance but restorative in quality with nourishing aloe and soft fabrics.</p>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B01J5BIFJW/" />
	</div>
	<p>This set of six socks from Enerwear includes includes black and gray styles for easy outfit pairings.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> These modal-polyester-blend socks have added durability in the heel and toe as well as added traction, thanks to their modal and Lycra treads for stable, all-day wear. Their aloe infusion helps to protect dry and cracked feet from chafing and irritations.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> These may fit tight on the calf.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07V1LCTR1/" />
	</div>
	<p>Made from a blend of modal, nylon, polyester, spandex and other fibers, oBolvs socks come in a classic crew design with a set of six.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> They also help wick away sweat thanks to their ventilated, breathable top panels and added odor-controlling technology. In addition to aloe vera, they're also infused with vitamin E.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> These may shrink if not dried properly.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07C3QX7J5/" />
	</div>
	<p>MediPeds uses a blend of cotton, polyester and spandex in this set of three roll-top socks.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>These knit, roll-top socks are soft and non-restrictive as well as aloe-infused to ease callused and cracked feet.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> These fit tight and may roll down more than banded-top socks.</p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Treat Your Feet in These Soothing Lavender-Infused Socks</title>
		<author>Claudia Miller</author>		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 16:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<link>https://footwearnews.com/2020/shop/socks/best-lavender-infused-socks-1202902571/</link>
					<amzn:heroImage>https://pmcfootwearnews.files.wordpress.com/2020/01/minxny-socks.jpg</amzn:heroImage>
							<amzn:heroImageCaption>Amazon</amzn:heroImageCaption>
					<amzn:indexContent>False</amzn:indexContent>
		<amzn:products>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B077ZL57GJ/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Dr. Scholl's Soothing Low Cut Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[For a plush style without too much added bulk, try these soft yarn socks from Dr. Scholl’s.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Top Knit Sock]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B007N5Y8F8/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[MinxNY Fluffy Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Enjoy the feel of fluffy socks with added soothing benefits.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Top Fluffy Sock]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07FB2YWVS/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[NatraCure Moisturizing Gel Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Restore your feet to better health in NatraCure’s socks.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Top Gel Sock]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
				</amzn:products>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Lavender is said to have restorative properties to help with anything from reducing insomnia to relieving pain. When infused into socks, it provides aid to dry skin, soothes irritation and can even work to help combat fungal infections. Our selection of soothing lavender socks will help simplify your search for the perfect pair. These sets include various styles like knit low-cut options or fuzzy crew socks from brands like Dr. Scholl&#8217;s, NatraCure and more. Wear these pairs around the house or overnight to sleep for continuous relief.</p>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B077ZL57GJ/" />
	</div>
	<p>Dr. Scholl's lavender-infused socks are made from 99% polyester with a touch of added spandex for stretchiness. Meanwhile, soft yarn wraps your feet in coziness. They come in a two-pack or as a single pair.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> These socks are also infused with vitamin E for moisturizing relief; they feature a smooth-toe design to reduce irritation and grips on the sole for added traction.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> These are one size fits 4 to 10.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B007N5Y8F8/" />
	</div>
	<p>This two-pack of crew socks from MinxNY includes one solid and one print pair, both made from cozy, fluffy fabric and with a dotted grip underfoot.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>Infused with lavender to reduce stress and to relieve pain, MinxNY's socks have micro-capsule technology to keep the scent locked in wash after wash.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> The grip dots may be bothersome on certain feet.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07FB2YWVS/" />
	</div>
	<p>NatraCure's equipped these ankle socks with nonslip bottoms and fabric made from 99% polyester and 1% spandex. They're lavender scented.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> The gel lining of these socks is made to slowly release therapeutic essential oils, including jojoba and olive oil, as you wear them.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> These socks are one size fits most.</p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Get the Support You Crave in These Cushioned Running Socks for Men</title>
		<author>Claudia Miller</author>		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 16:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<link>https://footwearnews.com/2020/shop/socks/best-cushioned-running-socks-1202902562/</link>
					<amzn:heroImage>https://pmcfootwearnews.files.wordpress.com/2020/01/thorlos-socks.jpg</amzn:heroImage>
							<amzn:heroImageCaption>Amazon</amzn:heroImageCaption>
					<amzn:indexContent>False</amzn:indexContent>
		<amzn:products>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07MFZ7BH9/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Thorlos Max Cushion Running Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Keep feet dry and padded in all the right places with Thorlos’ socks.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Top Pick]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07GZ92Y6W/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Joynée Athletic Cushion Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Get support for your feet where you need it most in these breathable crew socks.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best With Arch Support]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07HFZVVJV/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Coovan Premium Athletic Crew Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Coovan’s socks are made to stay put throughout your run.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Also Consider]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
				</amzn:products>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When on a run, crew socks can be very useful; not only do they block your ankle from the elements like water, dirt and wind but they also provide added compression to protect the muscles in your calves and lower legs. FN found cushioned crew socks for men that are sure to be a hit on your next go around the track. From brands including Coovan and Thorlo, they feature reinforced padding in the forefront and heel to help absorb shock with every stride. Built for high-endurance activities, these socks are made to last and stay put, even during any length of run.</p>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07MFZ7BH9/" />
	</div>
	<p>Made from 86% acrylic, 12% nylon and 2% elastic, Thorlos' socks use the brand's signature Thor-Lon fibers to wick away sweat and keep feet dry.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> This sock features padding in the heel and forefoot that's designed to reduce blisters, moisture, pain and pressure when running.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>The brand recommends turning these inside out when machine washing.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07GZ92Y6W/" />
	</div>
	<p>Joynée's socks are made from 90% polyester and 10% spandex for a breathable and durable wear that stretches to fit your foot.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> This pack includes six pairs of high-endurance socks. The brand's Max Cushioning in areas of high impact like the heel and front of the foot, and added arch support help protect feet during runs.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> The sizing is one size fits most.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07HFZVVJV/" />
	</div>
	<p>Coovan uses a mix of polyester and spandex in these socks that come in a pack of six.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> These socks have full-thickness cushioned bottoms as well as a reinforced heel and toe for enhanced durability; they also are equipped with a ribbed leg and cuffs to keep them from slipping down.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> These may fit tight on thicker calves.</p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stop Blisters in Their Tracks With These Protective Running Socks</title>
		<author>Claudia Miller</author>		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 15:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<link>https://footwearnews.com/2020/shop/socks/best-anti-blister-socks-1202902569/</link>
					<amzn:heroImage>https://pmcfootwearnews.files.wordpress.com/2020/01/thorlos-roll-top-socks.jpg</amzn:heroImage>
							<amzn:heroImageCaption>Amazon</amzn:heroImageCaption>
					<amzn:indexContent>False</amzn:indexContent>
		<amzn:products>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B0009MZUO0/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Thorlos Cushion Rolltop Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Everyone can experience the benefits of Thorlos’ cushioned socks.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Unisex]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B00DHKY0EC/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[FootJoy Roll-Top Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[FootJoy’s roll-top socks are made to protect your feet.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best for Men]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B0140QF3NS/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Gold Toe Aquafx Zone Tab Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Keep feet protected and cushioned in Gold Toe’s socks.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best for Women]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
				</amzn:products>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Picking the right socks requires a trustworthy choice when heading out on a run; they need to feature the right amount of material to prevent friction between your skin and the back of your shoe. From unisex styles to those with gender-specific sizing, we&#8217;ve compiled a range of top blister-blocking running socks to fit any need or preference. In addition to featuring a handy roll-top hem or heel tab, these socks are also made with breathable materials and mesh panels to prevent sweat that can also lead to angry blisters. What&#8217;s more, they include reinforced padding and double-layered fabrics for long-lasting wear and comfort.</p>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B0009MZUO0/" />
	</div>
	<p>Thorlos combines acrylic, nylon and elastic to make these roll-top socks with moisture-wicking fibers.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> The design of these socks protects the back of your heel and is equipped with padding in the heel and forefoot to reduce blisters and rubbing.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> These are thicker than expected.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B00DHKY0EC/" />
	</div>
	<p>FootJoy uses 77% combed cotton, 22% nylon and 1% Lycra in this three-pack of socks.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> These socks have a comfort-seam toe enclosure to keep from ripping; they also include double-layering in the heel to protect from abrasion and blisters.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> These run small.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B0140QF3NS/" />
	</div>
	<p>Made with a blend of rayon, cotton, nylon and spandex, Gold Toet's socks have a heel tab for extra protection.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> These socks have a reinforced toe and a deep Y-shaped heel to protect your skin from abrasions and rubbing; they're also moisture-wicking.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> These may slip down your foot.</p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Roll-Top Crew Socks for Women That Won&#8217;t Restrict Your Calves</title>
		<author>Claudia Miller</author>		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 15:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<link>https://footwearnews.com/2020/shop/socks/best-roll-top-socks-women-1202902570/</link>
					<amzn:heroImage>https://pmcfootwearnews.files.wordpress.com/2020/01/gold-toe-socks.jpg</amzn:heroImage>
							<amzn:heroImageCaption>Amazon</amzn:heroImageCaption>
					<amzn:indexContent>False</amzn:indexContent>
		<amzn:products>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B01D3JI092/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[K. Bell Relaxed Roll Top Crew Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[You’ll want to wear K. Bell’s soft cotton socks all day, every day.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Top Cotton Roll Top Sock]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07TYGN9C3/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Gold Toe Roll Top Crew Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Gold Toe’s socks keep up with your daily actions.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Knit Roll Top Sock]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07C3QX7J5/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[MediPeds Roll Top Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Protect and repair dry feet in MediPeds’ aloe-infused socks.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Aloe-Infused Roll Top Sock]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
				</amzn:products>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Some footwear fans may prefer roll-top socks over cuffed socks for everyday wear because they don&#8217;t contain elastic or compress the ankles and calves. If you find yourself on the roll-top sock team, look no further. Our list of great roll-top crew socks for women includes pairs from Gold Toe, MediPeds and more with a style for every need. These feature fabrics like soft cotton and cozy knit materials, all hitting mid-calf or above without feeling too tight or leaving band marks on your skin. Shop styles in stripes, neutral tones and more.</p>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B01D3JI092/" />
	</div>
	<p>K. Bell's are 70% cotton with an added mix of nylon and spandex for ideal stretch.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> These soft socks have a non-binding, relaxed rolltop for easy wear.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>These socks are one size fits most.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07TYGN9C3/" />
	</div>
	<p>Gold Toe's socks hit at mid-calf with a rolled top for maximum comfort.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>This three-pack features socks made with spandex and other fibers knit together to stretch to your foot's shape while remaining tight enough to stay up.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>These socks only fit women's shoe sizes 6 to 9.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07C3QX7J5/" />
	</div>
	<p>Made from 74% cotton, 23% polyester and 3% lycra, MediPeds' socks have a smooth, soft-knit feel.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> These roll-top socks are infused with aloe vera to help keep feet moisturized and soothed no matter how dry and rough they are.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> These fit tight.</p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Spice Up Any Outfit With These Fishnet Thigh-High Stockings</title>
		<author>Allie Fasanella</author>		<pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 02:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<link>https://footwearnews.com/2020/shop/womens/best-fishnet-thigh-high-stockings-1202900898/</link>
					<amzn:heroImage>https://pmcfootwearnews.files.wordpress.com/2020/01/untitled-10.jpg</amzn:heroImage>
							<amzn:heroImageCaption>Amazon</amzn:heroImageCaption>
					<amzn:indexContent>False</amzn:indexContent>
		<amzn:products>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B079YX6671/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Leg Avenue Fishnet Thigh Highs]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[These Leg Avenue fishnets are offered in an assortment of standout neon colors.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Top Pick]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B074S497H1/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Sofsy Fishnet Thigh Highs]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Sofsy’s fishnet thigh-highs are designed to retain their shape and fit like a second skin.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Honorable Mention]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07WSB4QS7/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Honenna Fishnet Thigh Highs]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[These stockings are stretchy and come in multiple sizes for different body types.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Bang for Your Buck]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
				</amzn:products>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Fishnet thigh-high stockings instantly add an  edge to your look. Wear them as an eye-catching addition under ripped jeans, peeking out from the hem of pants or with a dress as the focal point of the outfit. No matter which way you choose to wear them, it&#8217;s crucial that your pair stays up so they don&#8217;t end up being a hassle. Consider this your ultimate guide to some of the best fishnet thigh-high stockings you can buy. Each pair of stockings we chose is made with nylon, which is known for its strength, elasticity, smoothness and abrasion resistance. These options should offer you plenty of wear.</p>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B079YX6671/" />
	</div>
	<p>These thigh-highs feature a 100% nylon construction and an elastic band at the top.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>They're available in a variety of colors including a four pack with neon hues.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>They may roll down without a garter belt on some wearers.<strong></strong></p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B074S497H1/" />
	</div>
	<p>These fishnets are also equipped with a silicone lace band that should maintain its tension, stickiness and elasticity over time.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>These are offered in seven colors and three sizes.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>They run somewhat small.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07WSB4QS7/" />
	</div>
	<p>These contain mostly nylon with a hint of spandex for ultimate stretchiness and have a lace top.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>A silicone band at the top keeps them in place. They come in six colors and multiple sizes.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>Some may find them to be a little thin.</p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cute Thigh-High Socks That Will Take You Back to the 90s</title>
		<author>Allie Fasanella</author>		<pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 01:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<link>https://footwearnews.com/2020/shop/socks/best-thigh-high-socks-1202900869/</link>
					<amzn:heroImage>https://pmcfootwearnews.files.wordpress.com/2020/01/thigh-high-socks.jpg</amzn:heroImage>
							<amzn:heroImageCaption>Amazon</amzn:heroImageCaption>
					<amzn:indexContent>False</amzn:indexContent>
		<amzn:products>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B074TDRF5B/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Moon Wood Thigh High Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[These knit socks are incredibly soft and breathable for maximum comfort.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[The Cable Knit Style]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B01I2FM4ZI/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[TeeHee Set of 3 OTK Socks]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Not only are they cute, but these cuffed cable-knit socks are breathable so feet can stay dry and fresh.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Also Consider Cable Knit Style]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B01DEA9V84/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Leg Avenue Athletic Thigh Highs]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[These athletic-inspired socks come in a wide range of colors to choose from and shouldn’t fall down.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[The Sporty Style]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
				</amzn:products>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Thigh-high socks are a great way to add 90s-inspired flair to any outfit, whether you&#8217;re wearing a dress, mini skirt or shorts. It can be super frustrating, though, if they&#8217;re scratchy, too thin or keep slipping down your thighs, all of which will send them back to your sock drawer. To help you find the best style for your money, we compiled a few of our favorite options on the market. We incorporated a variety of styles on our list, including over-the-knee socks with a cable-knit design and thigh-highs offering an athletic, Sporty Spice–inspired look.</p>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B074TDRF5B/" />
	</div>
	<p>These are made of 80% cotton and 20% stretchy yarn with a classic cable-knit pattern.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>They're also available in a two-pack with a gray and black option. High stretchy elastic cuffs keep them from sliding down.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>They may be a little long for some.<strong></strong></p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B01I2FM4ZI/" />
	</div>
	<p>These cable knit socks feature 90% acrylic, which is soft, warm, lightweight and quick-drying.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>They're also made with spandex for additional stretch and polyester for durability. They're offered in additional colors.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>They run somewhat small.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B01DEA9V84/" />
	</div>
	<p>These two-stripe ribbed socks are made of mostly polyester with a hint of spandex for added elasticity.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>Elastic bands at the top prevent them from sliding down. They're available in eight colors.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>Some wearers may find them to be slightly short.</p>
<p><strong></strong></p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sheer Thigh-High Stockings That Are Made to Stay Up</title>
		<author>Allie Fasanella</author>		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 22:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<link>https://footwearnews.com/2020/shop/womens/sheer-thigh-high-stockings-amazon-1202900754/</link>
					<amzn:heroImage>https://pmcfootwearnews.files.wordpress.com/2020/01/untitled-9.jpg</amzn:heroImage>
							<amzn:heroImageCaption>Amazon</amzn:heroImageCaption>
					<amzn:indexContent>False</amzn:indexContent>
		<amzn:products>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B003R9FS58/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Dreamgirl Thigh-High Stockings]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[These stockings are simple, chic and accessible.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Top Pick]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B01253M4HQ/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Hanes Silk Reflections Thigh Highs]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Hanes Silk Reflections stockings are moisture-wicking to keep you dry.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Honorable Mention]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07R4WFCBN/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[GhostCat Thigh Highs]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[These thigh-high stockings are durable and should stay comfortably in place.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Honorable Mention]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
				</amzn:products>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Thigh-high stockings can be a more comfortable alternative to wearing full-length stockings, but only if they stay up properly. With this in mind, we took it upon ourselves to curate a list of the best sheer thigh-high stockings for women. We love the sheer look because it pairs equally well with closed toed pumps and open-toed pumps and sandals. When rounding up our picks, we looked for styles made with strong elastic and abrasion-resistant nylon. Each option is durable yet stretchy and designed to stay in place so you don&#8217;t have to worry about yours slipping down or bunching up. We included two options with flattering lace tops and another style with a pared-down look.</p>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B003R9FS58/" />
	</div>
	<p>This simple pair features 100% nylon construction and a stylish back seam.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>They come in black, red and white.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>Some may find the thick band around the top a little tight.<strong></strong></p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B01253M4HQ/" />
	</div>
	<p>These silky stockings have a lacy spandex band at the top for ultimate stretchy comfort.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>Cool Comfort fabric treatment wicks away moisture to keep you feeling cool and dry. They're offered in three sizes and seven colors and come as a pack of three.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>Some may find they run a bit small.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07R4WFCBN/" />
	</div>
	<p>These thigh-high stockings contain 85% nylon and 15% spandex with a peacock lace top design.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>A nonslip silicone band prevents them from falling down. They're offered in five colors and a value pack of five features a range of shades.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>They may also be slightly small for some.<strong></strong></p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lacy Thigh-High Stockings for a Bold Look</title>
		<author>Allie Fasanella</author>		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 01:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<link>https://footwearnews.com/2020/shop/womens/best-lace-thigh-high-stockings-1202900154/</link>
					<amzn:heroImage>https://pmcfootwearnews.files.wordpress.com/2020/01/sofsy-lace-sheer-thigh-high-stockings.jpg</amzn:heroImage>
							<amzn:heroImageCaption>Amazon</amzn:heroImageCaption>
					<amzn:indexContent>False</amzn:indexContent>
		<amzn:products>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B000ZHDH94/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Dreamgirl Fishnet Stockings]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[If you’re a fan of fishnets, you can’t go wrong with these lace-top stockings.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Fishnet Design]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B002QQCJLY/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Leg Avenue Lace Thigh Highs]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[These Leg Avenue stockings are perfect if you want to pull off an ultra-lacy look.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best All-Lace Style]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B06Y1WB681/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Sofsy Thigh-High Stockings]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[These sheer thigh-highs are offered in a wide variety of colors and sizes.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Sheer Style]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
				</amzn:products>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A pair of lacy thigh-high stockings can add some oomph to your look, but, for obvious reasons, it&#8217;s imperative that they&#8217;re durable, comfortable and stay in place without rolling down. With this in mind, we rounded up some of the best lacy thigh-high stockings on the market. We chose styles made with strong, abrasion-resistant fabrics like nylon and polyester that are soft and not itchy. Two options on our list include lacy tops featuring silicone rubber to prevent them from falling down, while one pick delivers a bold all-over lace design.</p>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B000ZHDH94/" />
	</div>
	<p>These nylon-blend thigh-highs feature a classic fishnet design and a lace top with silicone to ensure they stay up.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>They come in black, nude and white. Spandex delivers a better fit.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>Some wearers may find them a little long.<strong></strong></p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B002QQCJLY/" />
	</div>
	<p>These stockings are made of strong, anti-wrinkle polyester and feature a lacy rose print from toe to thigh.</p>
<p><strong style="font-family:-apple-system, BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen-Sans, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;">Pros: </strong>They're offered in three other lace designs.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>They may be too short on taller women.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B06Y1WB681/" />
	</div>
	<p>These sheer stockings are also made with stretchy and silky nylon and have a lace silicone stay-up top, too.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>They come in black, navy, natural, gray and tan. You can choose from 15 or 20 denier hose. Sizes range from XS to XXL.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>These may run slightly big.</p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>These Clear Wedges Will Go With Everything In Your Closet</title>
		<author>Allie Fasanella</author>		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 23:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<link>https://footwearnews.com/2020/shop/sandals/best-clear-wedges-1202900122/</link>
					<amzn:heroImage>https://pmcfootwearnews.files.wordpress.com/2020/01/jessica-simpson-seena.jpg</amzn:heroImage>
							<amzn:heroImageCaption>Amazon</amzn:heroImageCaption>
					<amzn:indexContent>False</amzn:indexContent>
		<amzn:products>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07H9K9M42/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Steve Madden Sunrise Sandal]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Steve Madden’s Sunrise sandal features plenty of cushioning underfoot.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Espadrille-Style Clear Wedge]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07K8GT2D5/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Cape Robbin Wedge]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[These sandals have a bold transparent wedge heel that’s sky-high.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best All-Over Clear Wedge]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07N4SH1CL/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Jessica Simpson Seena Sandal]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Jessica Simpson’s chic Seena sandal deliver a subtle boost of height.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Clear Cork Wedge]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
				</amzn:products>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Transparent heels and sandals, in particular, seem to be everywhere these days, from runways to celebrity wardrobes. If you&#8217;ve been wanting to try the clear heel trend, a wedge can be a great place to start, especially since they&#8217;re generally easier to walk in than stilettos. To help narrow down your search, we rounded up some of our favorite styles worth investing in. We included a range of styles for you to consider, from espadrille-inspired options to all-over clear wedges that would surely earn Kim Kardashian&#8217;s seal of approval.</p>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07H9K9M42/" />
	</div>
	<p>These sandals have a thick clear vinyl vamp strap, a thinner toe strap and a stylish jute-wrapped wedge heel measuring over 4 inches high.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> A 1.5-inch platform adds some extra height.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>They may run a bit small.</p>
<p><strong></strong></p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07K8GT2D5/" />
	</div>
	<p>This style features one clear PVC vamp strap with a peep-toe design and an approximately 4.25-inch heel.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>They have a soft faux suede and faux leather insole. In addition to beige, the sandal can be purchased with a pink, lime green, orange, blue or black footbed. The shoe also comes in an option with a cork footbed.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>They may run somewhat wide.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07N4SH1CL/" />
	</div>
	<p>These sandals are equipped with a 3.5-inch cork wedge heel and two clear acrylic crossover straps.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>A cushy memory foam midsole enhances comfort for long-lasting wear.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>These also run slightly small.</p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gold Toe Rings to Add Shine to Your Everyday Look</title>
		<author>Elisa Lewittes</author>		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 21:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<link>https://footwearnews.com/2020/shop/womens/best-gold-toe-rings-amazon-1202900008/</link>
					<amzn:heroImage>https://pmcfootwearnews.files.wordpress.com/2020/01/best-gold-toe-rings-amazon.jpg</amzn:heroImage>
							<amzn:heroImageCaption>Amazon</amzn:heroImageCaption>
					<amzn:indexContent>False</amzn:indexContent>
		<amzn:products>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B008RFF3ZM/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[More Toe Rings Gold Toe Ring]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[This minimalist silhouette is a classic gold piece that will add some glamour to your everyday look.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Classic Band]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B008JF1KEI/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Ritastephens Gold Crossover Toe Ring]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[This sparkling ring will elevate any ensemble and can double as a finger ring, too.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Embellished Toe Ring]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B00DVXU3XC/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[California Toe Rings 14K Gold-Filled Toe Ring]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[This gold-filled toe ring makes a subtle yet stylish statement and is designed to withstand everyday wear.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Bang For Your Buck]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
				</amzn:products>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>While subtle, toe rings might be one of the most underrated accessories. This jewelry piece makes you feel polished and put together when you wear it with sandals or open-toed mules, making them perfect for a warm-weather vacation. When shopping for gold toe rings, make sure to seek out pieces made of real gold, so they don&#8217;t tarnish or turn your toes green. They should be suitable to wear in the shower and only need to be taken off to polish. Many toe rings can work well on your fingers, too. Read on to discover some of the best gold toe rings available now.</p>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B008RFF3ZM/" />
	</div>
	<p>This wide-band gold toe ring is made of 10K gold with a smooth, polished finish and rigid-edge detailing. The band is 3MM with an open back to make it adjustable in order to perfectly fit your toes.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> The simple design makes this piece versatile and easy to wear every day.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> Remember to check the size and dimensions if you have relatively small or big toes.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B008JF1KEI/" />
	</div>
	<p>The toe ring is made of 10K gold with a front crossover detail and cubic zirconia embellishments, which add effortless glamour to your everyday ensemble.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> The ring is slightly adjustable due to the front opening.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> Make sure to handle the ring with care, especially if you're wearing tighter shoes to ensure the stones don't come loose.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B00DVXU3XC/" />
	</div>
	<p>This toe ring has 14K gold filling, which makes it a more accessibly priced product, and embossed detailing for added aesthetic intrigue. The band is 2MM wide and adjustable.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> This toe ring offers an alternative to a pure gold ring that requires less upfront investment without sacrificing quality. Due to its 14K filling and adjustable design, this accessory should not turn your toes green, and you can customize the size for a better fit.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> Remember to check the ring dimensions, especially if you have wider toes.</p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>These Pretty Cubic Zirconia Toe Rings Will Put Extra Sparkle In Your Step</title>
		<author>Allie Fasanella</author>		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 20:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<link>https://footwearnews.com/2020/shop/womens/best-cubic-zirconia-toe-rings-amazon-1202899902/</link>
					<amzn:heroImage>https://pmcfootwearnews.files.wordpress.com/2020/01/ritastephens-1.jpg</amzn:heroImage>
							<amzn:heroImageCaption>Amazon</amzn:heroImageCaption>
					<amzn:indexContent>False</amzn:indexContent>
		<amzn:products>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B01FEGRU7A/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[GemStar USA]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Set with over 10 CZ stones, this toe ring delivers maximum sparkle.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Ultimate Sparkle]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B008BI4HZM/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Rita Stephens Toe Ring]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[This Rita Stephens toe ring has an intricate design and is made to last.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Most Unique Design]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B01G2OHUL4/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Hoops &amp; Loops Toe Ring]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[This toe ring delivers just the right amount of sparkle without breaking the bank.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[The 3-Stone Ring]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
				</amzn:products>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Getting a fresh pedicure isn&#8217;t the only thing you can do to make your feet look polished during sandal season. You may want to consider slipping on a toe ring made with cubic zirconia, a popular artificial gem that bears an incredible resemblance to diamonds yet is much less expensive. Ahead, shop some of our favorite cubic zirconia toe rings to add some sparkle to your jewelry collection. Each style included features a durable sterling silver band with open ends so you can adjust the size of the ring to help you get a perfect fit.</p>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B01FEGRU7A/" />
	</div>
	<p>In addition to a yellow gold finish, this style comes in a rose gold finish and classic silver. It contains 11 round stones.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>It's packaged in a convenient storage pouch.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>Some users may find it to be a tad small.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B008BI4HZM/" />
	</div>
	<p>This ornate crossover toe ring features two simple round stones.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>A rhodium finish helps prevents it from tarnishing.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> It may be a bit big for some</p>
<p><strong></strong></p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B01G2OHUL4/" />
	</div>
	<p>This toe ring is equipped with three round stones placed in the center and a special anti-tarnish coating.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>It comes in a satin pouch. It's offered in rose gold and yellow.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> Some may find the band to be too thick for their liking.</p>
<p><strong></strong></p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Best Back-Seam Tights for A Vintage-Inspired Look</title>
		<author>Claudia Miller</author>		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<link>https://footwearnews.com/2020/shop/womens/best-back-seam-tights-1202899838/</link>
					<amzn:heroImage>https://pmcfootwearnews.files.wordpress.com/2020/01/leg-avenue-tights.jpg</amzn:heroImage>
							<amzn:heroImageCaption>Amazon</amzn:heroImageCaption>
					<amzn:indexContent>False</amzn:indexContent>
		<amzn:products>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B01F5FT6DG/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Leg Avenue Back Seam Pantyhose]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Leg Avenue’s sheer stockings are a subtle and classic pick.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Sheer Style]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B00K2Z1HOG/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Spanx Scallop Backseam Pantyhose]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[This bold style is especially figure-flattering.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best With Tummy Control]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B0002QVACY/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Capezio Fishnet Tights]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[These fishnet tights offer an ultra-retro look.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Fishnet Style]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
				</amzn:products>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Back seam tights were popularized by pin-up models in the mid 20th century. Complete with exposed stitching up the back of the leg, these styles can still be rocked today for a sultry, retro-inspired look. To make your shopping a cinch, we rounded up some of our favorite back seam tights to shop now. From brands like Spanx and Capezio, these options are ideal for all sorts of settings, from the office to Halloween. Whether you&#8217;re in the market for a fishnet style or tummy-controlling tights, our list includes a style for every need.</p>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B01F5FT6DG/" />
	</div>
	<p>Leg Avenue's stockings are made from a mix of 80% nylon and 20% spandex for a mix of durability and stretch.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> These sheer tights have a thin back seam for a subtle effect.</p>
<p><strong style="font-family:-apple-system, BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen-Sans, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;">Cons:</strong><span style="font-family:-apple-system, BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen-Sans, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;"> As these are sheer, the fabric can be more prone to rips and snags.</span></p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B00K2Z1HOG/" />
	</div>
	<p>From Spanx's Assets by Sara Blakely line, these stockings are semi-sheer and have a scalloped back seam.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> These tights have the brand's signature tummy-control panels and compression panels on the thighs for a smooth, shapely finish.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> These run small.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B0002QVACY/" />
	</div>
	<p>Capezio uses 80% nylon and 20% spandex to make these fishnet tights, a style that dates back to the 20s.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> These also feature a subtle back seam.</p>
<p><strong style="font-family:-apple-system, BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen-Sans, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;">Cons:</strong><span style="font-family:-apple-system, BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen-Sans, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;"> The brand recommends hand washing these on cold and hanging them to dry.</span></p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Satin Thigh-High Stockings for A Luxe Look</title>
		<author>Claudia Miller</author>		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<link>https://footwearnews.com/2020/shop/womens/best-satin-thigh-high-stockings-1202899837/</link>
					<amzn:heroImage>https://pmcfootwearnews.files.wordpress.com/2020/01/marilyn-stockings.jpg</amzn:heroImage>
							<amzn:heroImageCaption>Amazon</amzn:heroImageCaption>
					<amzn:indexContent>False</amzn:indexContent>
		<amzn:products>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B000GIUUB0/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Leg Avenue Satin Thigh-High Stockings]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[These bow-accented stockings offer a slightly whimsical look.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Bow-Accented Style]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07R4WFCBN/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[GhostCat Thigh-High Stockings]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[For a high sheen, ultra-sultry style, try this pair from GhostCat.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best High Sheen Style]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B01791FJEE/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Marilyn Satin Thigh-High Stockings]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Mariyln’s stockings are the most barely-there look on our list.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Ultra-Sheer Style]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
				</amzn:products>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With their silky feel and subtly iridescent finish, satin thigh-high stockings add a luxurious touch to work dresses and amplify the elegance of more formal frocks. Ahead, we compiled some of our favorite satin thigh-high stockings to help you elevate your style. From brands like Leg Avenue, these sets all feature elasticated bands to keep the stocking upright. Many also come with their own unique accents for subtle flair, like bows or lacey trim. They&#8217;re all sheer styles but vary in their level of transparency, from bolder skin-baring options to those that keep you mostly covered up. Read on to find your perfect match.</p>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B000GIUUB0/" />
	</div>
	<p>Leg Avenue's stockings hit thigh-high and are made with stretchy spandex for a fit that moves with you.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> Leg Avenue's satin stockings are adorned with a bow at the top elastic band for a unique take on the style.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> These run long.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07R4WFCBN/" />
	</div>
	<p>GhostCat's stockings use a mix of nylon and spandex for a silky, stretchable feel.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>These shimmery stockings have an anti-skid silicone design so they stay put and a sultry peacock lace thick top band.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> These are one size fits most.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B01791FJEE/" />
	</div>
	<p>These stockings from Marilyn hit thigh-high with a thicker silicone band.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> They offer ultasheer coverage for those who prefer to shoe a little more skin.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> There is an exposed seam running up the back of the leg.</p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Opaque Thigh-High Stockings That Are Made to Stay Put</title>
		<author>Claudia Miller</author>		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 17:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<link>https://footwearnews.com/2020/shop/womens/best-thigh-high-stockings-opaque-1202899836/</link>
					<amzn:heroImage>https://pmcfootwearnews.files.wordpress.com/2020/01/mila-marutti-stockings.jpg</amzn:heroImage>
							<amzn:heroImageCaption>Amazon</amzn:heroImageCaption>
					<amzn:indexContent>False</amzn:indexContent>
		<amzn:products>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07M73Z7H9/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Mila Marutti Thigh-High Opaque Stockings]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Finish off your ensemble with Mila Marutti’s lace-topped stockings.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Lacey Style]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B003K0MBKY/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Leg Avenue Accent Thigh-High Stockings]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Leg Avenue’s bow-accented stockings are both sweet and stretchy.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Bow-Accented Stockings]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07PZ6QZZK/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Boao Thigh-High Stockings]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Get four opaque thigh-high stockings to wear for a range of occasions in this value-packed set.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Bang for Your Buck]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
				</amzn:products>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Finding a pair of tights that doesn&#8217;t slip down every few minutes is a masterful feat. For anyone who&#8217;s tired of these full-length styles that just never seem to stay put, it might be time to invest in thigh-high stockings. For your convenience, we&#8217;ve rounded up a selection of great opaque thigh-high stockings to add to your closet. These options feature elastic bands that are made to stay put without digging into your skin. They also offer opaque coverage, making them perfect for those who prefer a slightly more covered up look or want protection in cooler weather.</p>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07M73Z7H9/" />
	</div>
	<p>Mila Marutti's stockings are opaque and made with 40 denier nylon for durable wear.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>These stockings have a lace top with double silicone strips to keep them from sliding and slipping down the leg with a matte base.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> These may fit short on taller frames.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B003K0MBKY/" />
	</div>
	<p>These Leg Avenue stockings are made from 100% spandex and hit mid-thigh with an elastic band at the top.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>Small ribbon bows accent these stockings, available in a variety of shades and colorways.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> These run long.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07PZ6QZZK/" />
	</div>
	<p>Boao uses a soft mix of nylon and spandex for these smooth, banded-top stockings.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>These stockings come in a set of four different colors so you get four thigh-high opaque sets for an affordable price.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> The brand recommends hand-washing and air-drying these stockings.</p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Teens Will Adore These Cool Toe Ring Sets</title>
		<author>Allie Fasanella</author>		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 01:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<link>https://footwearnews.com/2020/shop/womens/best-toe-ring-sets-girls-amazon-1202899636/</link>
					<amzn:heroImage>https://pmcfootwearnews.files.wordpress.com/2020/01/jstyle-8-12pcs-adjustable-toe-rings-1.jpg</amzn:heroImage>
							<amzn:heroImageCaption>Amazon</amzn:heroImageCaption>
					<amzn:indexContent>False</amzn:indexContent>
		<amzn:products>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07S91B4J1/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Finrezio 8 Piece Set]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[These toe rings feature a variety of intricate designs to appreciate.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[The Platinum-Plated Option]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07L6F2K2Z/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Jstyle 8 Piece Set]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[These adorable toe rings are designed to deliver a comfortable fit that’s safe on all skin.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[The Hypoallergenic Option]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07HH9BWCV/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[FunRun Jewelry 2 Piece Set]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[These simple toe rings are offered in silver and gold to suit differing preferences.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[The Sterling Silver Option]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
				</amzn:products>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If you&#8217;re looking for a gift for the jewelry-loving girl in your life, consider a toe ring set. Toe rings make fun accessories during sandal season and when going barefoot at the beach or pool. With this in mind, we did some research and rounded up a list of our favorite options on the market that are perfect for teens and preteens. Each set we&#8217;ve included features adjustable styles in a range of designs, from intricate carvings to more simplistic options and those with a bit of bling.</p>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07S91B4J1/" />
	</div>
	<p>This set includes an assortment of shiny gold toe rings made from platinum-plated copper.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>These are also offered in rose gold. Their size is easily adjustable to fit most toes. They come in a velvet storage pouch.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>Some may find them too small.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07L6F2K2Z/" />
	</div>
	<p>These rings are made of stainless steel, so they won't irritate anyone with copper or nickel allergies. They're slightly adjustable to accommodate varying toe sizes.</p>
<p><strong style="font-family:-apple-system, BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen-Sans, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;">Pros: </strong>They also come in a convenient carrying bag to help prevent them from getting lost.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>They may start to tarnish somewhat after extended wear.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07HH9BWCV/" />
	</div>
	<p>These are made with sterling silver and mixed with an alloy for added strength and durability.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>They come in a storage pouch and are available in silver and gold.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>They may change color if worn in a pool.<strong></strong></p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chic Adjustable Toe Rings Anyone Can Wear</title>
		<author>Allie Fasanella</author>		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<link>https://footwearnews.com/2020/shop/womens/adjustable-toe-rings-amazon-1202899613/</link>
					<amzn:heroImage>https://pmcfootwearnews.files.wordpress.com/2020/01/toe-ring-1.jpg</amzn:heroImage>
							<amzn:heroImageCaption>Amazon</amzn:heroImageCaption>
					<amzn:indexContent>False</amzn:indexContent>
		<amzn:products>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07DY6MSCT/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[River Island Jewelry Toe Ring]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[This toe ring will add a little sparkle to your every step.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Top Pick]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B01FS81EKI/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Metal Factory Toe Ring]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[This simple silver toe ring is great for those who love a layered look.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Bang for Your Buck]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B074TLHKMW/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Toe Rings and Things Braid Stack]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[The mixed metal style offers a cool boho look.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Also Consider]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
				</amzn:products>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Adding a toe ring to your look when wearing sandals or hitting the beach barefoot is a great way to make a subtle jewelry statement. It&#8217;s imperative to get one that fits right though. For an easy solution, try a toe ring that&#8217;s adjustable to accommodate different toe sizes. With that in mind, we rounded up some of our favorite adjustable toe rings on the market. Each shimmery style we&#8217;ve included is made with sterling silver, which is known for its durability. Bonus: Sterling silver jewelry tends to be accessibly priced, so you can stay on-trend without spending a fortune.</p>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07DY6MSCT/" />
	</div>
	<p>This toe ring features a sterling silver band and a 3D heart design featuring cubic zirconia stones.</p>
<p><strong style="font-family:-apple-system, BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen-Sans, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;">Pros: </strong>A coating of anti-tarnish protection ensures this style won't lose its shine. It's also available in rose gold and comes in a free velvet pouch.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>Some may find that it rotates a bit.</p>
<p><strong></strong></p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B01FS81EKI/" />
	</div>
	<p>This 3-bar toe ring is also made with durable, malleable sterling silver.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>It's packed in a neat gift box.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>It runs a tad big.</p>
<p><strong></strong></p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B074TLHKMW/" />
	</div>
	<p>This sterling silver toe ring has 2 silver bars and a 14k gold fill braid design in the center for a laidback feel.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>This one also comes neatly packaged.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>Some may find it too lightweight.</p>
<p><strong></strong></p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Puka Shell Anklets Are a Fashion-Girl Favorite</title>
		<author>Elisa Lewittes</author>		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 21:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<link>https://footwearnews.com/2020/shop/womens/best-puka-shell-anklet-vsco-90s-1202899513/</link>
					<amzn:heroImage>https://pmcfootwearnews.files.wordpress.com/2020/01/puka-shell-anklet-feature.jpg</amzn:heroImage>
							<amzn:heroImageCaption>muna el-rihani/Shutterstock</amzn:heroImageCaption>
					<amzn:indexContent>False</amzn:indexContent>
		<amzn:products>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07D6K31VN/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Potessa Cowrie Shell Ankle Bracelet]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Complete with metallic accents, this simple accessory is sure to elevate any casual outfit.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Top Pick]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07SK28J83/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Fesciory Puka Shell Adjustable Anklet]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[This ankle bracelet adds a subtle yet beachy element to any ensemble.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Honorable Mention]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B082W4SB3Q/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Cilkus Necklace and Anklet Puka Shell Set]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Fully embrace the puka shell aesthetic with this matching necklace and anklet set. The anklet can double as a bracelet, too (depending on your wrist size).]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Bang for Your Buck]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
				</amzn:products>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the rise of &#8217;90s nostalgia to the new &#8220;VSCO girl&#8221; aesthetic, puka shell (also called cowrie shell) embellishments have resurfaced on the fashion scene. And it&#8217;s not hard to understand the appeal. The beach-inspired accessory adds a retro feel to any warm-weather outfit, from sundresses to jeans skirts and everything in between. Even if you wouldn&#8217;t consider your style boho, these anklets also pair well with edgier, moto-inspired outfits for an unexpected twist. What&#8217;s more, they&#8217;re also mainly in neutral hues, making them easy to pair with any outfit&#8217;s color palette. Read on to shop some of our favorite puka shell anklets that are available now.</p>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07D6K31VN/" />
	</div>
	<p>This ankle bracelet is made with natural and gold-painted cowrie shells as well as cowrie beads and a wax cord. The 7.8-inch cord is made to stretch up to 15 inches, with a slipknot to customize the size to perfectly suit your ankle.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> The adjustable detailing makes this bracelet highly versatile and likely to fit nearly anyone's ankle.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> T<span style="font-family:-apple-system, BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen-Sans, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;">his piece likely will not double as a wrist bracelet for the average woman. </span></p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07SK28J83/" />
	</div>
	<p>This handmade puka shell anklet is available in a variety of colors, from black and beige to those with turquoise or gold detailing. The bracelet features a sliding cord and wax twine to adjust the strap to fit your ankle.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> The anklet should fit nearly any ankle size, and there are a lot of color options to choose from.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> Some users may find it's slightly difficult to adjust.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B082W4SB3Q/" />
	</div>
	<p>The necklace and anklet are both made with natural shells, jade cords and adjustable pearl buckles. The necklace ranges from 16 to 18 inches long, and the anklet ranges from 7 to 14 inches.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> The two-piece set makes this a value-packed offer. The adjustable cords make these jewelry items highly versatile and able to fit most people.</p>
<p><strong>Cons</strong>: The necklace clasp might be difficult to take on and off alone, so have a friend or partner help you if necessary.</p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>These Waterproof Adjustable Anklets Are Perfect for Vacation</title>
		<author>Allie Fasanella</author>		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 19:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<link>https://footwearnews.com/2020/shop/womens/best-waterproof-beach-anklets-amazon-1202899497/</link>
					<amzn:heroImage>https://pmcfootwearnews.files.wordpress.com/2020/01/fancy-shiny-anklet-set.jpg</amzn:heroImage>
							<amzn:heroImageCaption>Amazon</amzn:heroImageCaption>
					<amzn:indexContent>False</amzn:indexContent>
		<amzn:products>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B072LYHSS5/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Pura Vida Originals Anklet]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[This beachy Pura Vida anklet is equipped to take on rain, surfing and showering.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Top Pick]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07S39TS1T/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Fancy Shiny Anklet Set]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[These braided, embellished anklets can be layered any way you like.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Honorable Mention]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07RQXRTHJ/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Manven Evil Eye Anklet Set]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[These waterproof anklets feature a subtle evil eye amulet, which is said to ward off misfortunate.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Bang for Your Buck]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
				</amzn:products>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If you&#8217;re looking to hit the beach and play in the surf while sporting an eye-catching anklet, it&#8217;s important that you find one that&#8217;s waterproof. Otherwise, it will likely deteriorate quickly or lose its color after you step in the ocean. Fortunately, a variety of brands make ankle bracelets that can get totally soaked and still hold up nicely. To help you find exactly what you&#8217;re looking for, we curated some of our favorite waterproof adjustable anklets featuring wax-coated strings. Each of our picks will add a pop of color to your beach look.</p>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B072LYHSS5/" />
	</div>
	<p>This anklet features blue, yellow and orange wax-coated strings and the brand's signature iron-coated copper "P" charm.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> An adjustable slipknot band widens 3–6 inches to accommodate different ankle sizes.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>Some may find it a little flimsy.</p>
<p><strong></strong></p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07S39TS1T/" />
	</div>
	<p>This set of three anklets is also made from wax-coated string. The black and gray braided ones are decorated with small coin-like charms.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>You can adjust the slipknot 8–12 inches.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>They may loosen after a while.</p>
<p><strong></strong></p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07RQXRTHJ/" />
	</div>
	<p>With this option, you get six simple string anklets in various colors and each has an evil eye charm.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>You can adjust the sliding knot closure up to 14 inches.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>Some may wish they were slightly thicker.</p>
<p><strong></strong></p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stunning Transparent Sandals for Every Budget</title>
		<author>Claudia Miller</author>		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 17:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<link>https://footwearnews.com/2020/shop/sandals/best-clear-heels-sandals-1202899343/</link>
					<amzn:heroImage>https://pmcfootwearnews.files.wordpress.com/2020/01/scutz-clear-heels.jpg</amzn:heroImage>
							<amzn:heroImageCaption>Amazon</amzn:heroImageCaption>
					<amzn:indexContent>False</amzn:indexContent>
		<amzn:products>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07SH8JRHY/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Schutz Blanck PVC Sandals]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Schutz’s clear sandals are perfect for parties and formal occasions.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[The Party Style]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B01M4QPP52/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Steve Madden Clearer Sandals]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Able to work with both jeans and cocktail dresses, this classic style promises to be a new closet staple.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Most Versatile]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B01LX8SBOL/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Cape Robbin Maria-2 Block Heels]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Get in on the clear heel trend without breaking the bank with a pair from Cape Robbin.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Bang For Your Buck]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
				</amzn:products>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>To the editors of FN, there&#8217;s no better way to stand out from the crowd than with a bold pair of shoes. One of our latest favorite styles that fills the bill? Transparent sandals. Varying in silhouette and height, these options from Schutz, Steve Madden and more are sure to earn you compliments and double-takes anywhere you go. They all feature see-through heels and can match many outfits thanks to their neutral colors and PVC straps. Plus, they span a range of price points, so you&#8217;re bound to find a style that fits your budget nicely. Read on to find your dream pair.</p>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07SH8JRHY/" />
	</div>
	<p>Schutz's block heel mules feature two clear front straps adorned with crystal appliqués for a show-stopping look.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> The heel measures four inches for leg-lengthening effects.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> These run small.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B01M4QPP52/" />
	</div>
	<p>Steve Madden uses PVC straps around the ankle and the toe to create this 4-inch heel.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>The adjustable buckle on the ankle strap allows for a customizable fit while a rounded, thicker heel creates a stable base and a modern look.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> It's suggested to size up from your normal sizing.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B01LX8SBOL/" />
	</div>
	<p>Complete with a 4.25-inch square heel, Cape Robbin's ankle strap sandals offer a sleek, trend-forward look.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> These trendy heels come in a variety of heights and colors, all at an accessible price.</p>
<p><strong style="font-family:-apple-system, BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen-Sans, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;">Cons:</strong><span style="font-family:-apple-system, BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen-Sans, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;"> These fit narrow.</span></p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fierce Gladiator-Style Heels to Shop for Now</title>
		<author>Claudia Miller</author>		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 16:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<link>https://footwearnews.com/2020/shop/sandals/best-gladiator-style-heels-1202899200/</link>
					<amzn:heroImage>https://pmcfootwearnews.files.wordpress.com/2020/01/gladiator-heels.jpg</amzn:heroImage>
							<amzn:heroImageCaption>Shutterstock</amzn:heroImageCaption>
					<amzn:indexContent>False</amzn:indexContent>
		<amzn:products>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07JN1XLV2/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Aldo Rorka Heels]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Aldo’s gladiator-style heels incorporate braided straps for a unique take on the trend.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best from Aldo]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07KYRTQJF/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[BCBGeneration Jean Sandals]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[The metal detailing on BCBGeneration’s cage heels make these particularly sleek.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best from BCBGeneration]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07KG6GG6L/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Calvin Klein Gili Sandals]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[A slightly more subtle take on the style, Calvin Klein’s heels can be easily adjusted to find the right fit for you.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best from Calvin Klein]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
				</amzn:products>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Inspired by the Greek and Roman sandals of antiquity, strappy, cage-style heels are a svelte and eye-catching shoe style. A range of brands from Calvin Klein to Aldo offer their modern takes on the look, so you can easily spice up your wardrobe for the warm weather season. Ahead, shop some of the chicest gladiator-style heels on the market. Offered in both faux and genuine leather finishes as well as colors ranging from vibrant red to deep green, there is a pair for every taste. They also look much more expensive than they actually are.</p>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07JN1XLV2/" />
	</div>
	<p>These cage-style sandals feature roped details and a 4.25-inch heel. They're a real standout when done in red.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>A zipper along the heel allows for easy on and off access.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> The straps are nonadjustable and may fit tighter or looser, depending on the individual foot.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07KYRTQJF/" />
	</div>
	<p>BCBGeneration's leather sandals feature subtle hardware on the straps and a 4-inch covered heel.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> The look can easily be dressed up or down for a range of occasions.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> Colors may appear different online than in person.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07KG6GG6L/" />
	</div>
	<p>These genuine leather sandals feature two supportive ankle straps with adjustable buckles and an angled 4-inch heel.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> They come in forest green, silver, white and black.</p>
<p><strong>Cons:</strong> The straps may shift or slide slightly when walking.</p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>These Beaded Anklets Are The Perfect Warm Weather Accessories</title>
		<author>Allie Fasanella</author>		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 02:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<link>https://footwearnews.com/2020/shop/womens/best-beaded-anklets-amazon-1202899106/</link>
					<amzn:heroImage>https://pmcfootwearnews.files.wordpress.com/2020/01/starain-small-bead-anklet.jpg</amzn:heroImage>
							<amzn:heroImageCaption>Amazon</amzn:heroImageCaption>
					<amzn:indexContent>False</amzn:indexContent>
		<amzn:products>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07NBTWHQ6/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Pura Vida Beaded Anklet]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[This braided anklet is waterproof, making it perfect for the beach.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[The Waterproof Style]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07VM6PWYG/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Starain Beaded Anklet]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[This colorful anklet is eye-catching and ideal for sensitive skin.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[The Set]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B008WQNHS6/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Hempnotic Jewelry Anklet]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[This hemp beaded anklet is simple and versatile.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[The Hemp Style]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
				</amzn:products>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Adding an anklet to your look when you&#8217;re wearing sandals or hitting the beach barefoot is a great way to stand out. And some of the prettiest and most popular styles feature beadwork. There&#8217;s a wide variety of options on the market, so to help narrow down your choices, we rounded up some of our favorite beaded anklets to show off when it&#8217;s warm out. Each pick will complement an already vibrant outfit or amplify a simple look by adding a pop of color at the ankle. We&#8217;ve even included a waterproof braided style to withstand wear and tear on your next trip to the pool or a seaside vacation.</p>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07NBTWHQ6/" />
	</div>
	<p>This anklet features wax-coated, waterproof threading and ornate silver beads.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> It comes in turquoise and lavender. An adjustable slipknot design allows it to fit different ankle sizes.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>The color may fade a bit after continued wear.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07VM6PWYG/" />
	</div>
	<p>This anklet features multicolored glass seed beads and measures eight inches long.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>The hypoallergenic 14K gold-plated extension chain is suitable for sensitive skin. It has a sturdy, reliable lobster claw clasp. These come in a pack of two.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>It may be somewhat big for smaller ankles.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B008WQNHS6/" />
	</div>
	<p>This 10-inch anklet features three hemp strands with an assortment of glass beads in various colors.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>It has a silver-plated lobster claw clasp.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>This one might also be a little big on some ankles.</p>
<p><strong></strong></p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stylish Sterling Silver Anklets You&#8217;ll Never Want to Take Off</title>
		<author>Allie Fasanella</author>		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 23:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<link>https://footwearnews.com/2020/shop/womens/best-sterling-silver-anklets-amazon-1202899058/</link>
					<amzn:heroImage>https://pmcfootwearnews.files.wordpress.com/2020/01/amazon-collection.jpg</amzn:heroImage>
							<amzn:heroImageCaption>Amazon</amzn:heroImageCaption>
					<amzn:indexContent>False</amzn:indexContent>
		<amzn:products>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B00AW64W2O/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Amazon Collection Anklet]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[This Amazon Collection anklet is simple, delicate and built for longevity.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Top Pick]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B072J3B6XB/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Hoops &amp; Loops Anklet]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[This sturdy anklet comes neatly packaged in a travel pouch.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Honorable Mention]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B0719HGZ9V/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Amberta Anklet]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[This dainty anklet comes in a variety of designs to suit different preferences.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Also Consider]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
				</amzn:products>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Many jewelry designers use sterling silver, an alloy made from pure silver and other trace metals, because of its malleability and durability. When taken care of properly, sterling silver pieces can last decades. It&#8217;s even stronger than gold, and unlike other metals such as nickel and brass, sterling silver isn&#8217;t likely to irritate your skin. For these reasons, it&#8217;s a great option if you&#8217;re looking for an anklet that&#8217;ll last you more than one warm weather season. With this in mind, we curated some of our favorite sterling silver anklets on the market. They&#8217;re all accessibly priced, too, so you don&#8217;t have to spend a fortune to add these cute accessories to your wardrobe.</p>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B00AW64W2O/" />
	</div>
	<p>This intricate option offers subtle sparkle.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>You can choose from a 9-inch or 10-inch anklet. It also comes in multiple color combinations.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>Some may find it's too short.</p>
<p><strong></strong></p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B072J3B6XB/" />
	</div>
	<p>This 9-inch anklet is equipped with a bismark chain, lobster claw closure and a 1-inch extender.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>It comes in a convenient carrying pouch. It's also offered in rose and yellow gold finishes.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>Some may prefer a thinner style.</p>
<p><strong></strong></p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B0719HGZ9V/" />
	</div>
	<p>This beaded chain anklet is 9 inches long with a 1-inch extender and features a reliable spring clasp.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>It comes with a free guide on how to keep, store and clean your silver jewelry, and there are eight unique designs to choose from.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>This may also be a bit tight for some.</p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>These Waterproof Knit Sneakers Will Actually Keep Your Feet Dry</title>
		<author>Allie Fasanella</author>		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 20:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<link>https://footwearnews.com/2020/shop/sneakers-deals/best-waterproof-sneakers-knit-1202898968/</link>
					<amzn:heroImage>https://pmcfootwearnews.files.wordpress.com/2020/01/sorel-womens-out-e28098n-about-plus-sneaker.jpg</amzn:heroImage>
							<amzn:heroImageCaption>Amazon</amzn:heroImageCaption>
					<amzn:indexContent>False</amzn:indexContent>
		<amzn:products>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07F8YFQ8W/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Sorel Out ‘N About Plus Sneakers]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Sorel’s Out ‘N About Plus sneakers for women are designed to keep feet dry and protected.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Most Stylish]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07FBQRRSQ/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Skechers Toston WP Sneakers]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[These Skechers sneakers for men will keep your socks from getting soggy in wet weather conditions.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Best Work Sneaker]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07XBS9C52/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Whitin Knit Sneakers]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[These simple unisex sneakers will go with anything and keep your feet dry.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[Most Versatile]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
				</amzn:products>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s not always ideal to wear clunky rubber boots when it&#8217;s wet outside. Enter the water-resistant knit sneaker. A variety of brands offers sneaker styles with waterproof knit constructions that are equipped to keep you dry when its raining cats and dogs. To ensure you find the best pair for your needs, we did some research and rounded up a few of our favorite options for men and women. We included sneakers from well-respected brands like Sorel, <a href="https://footwearnews.com/t/cole-haan/" id="auto-tag_cole-haan" data-tag="cole-haan">Cole Haan</a> and <a href="https://footwearnews.com/t/skechers/" id="auto-tag_skechers" data-tag="skechers">Skechers</a> for you to choose from. Each shoe has a classic lace-up silhouette and breathable uppers so feet don&#8217;t get too sweaty.</p>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07F8YFQ8W/" />
	</div>
	<p>This Sorel women's style has a waterproof bootie construction with front and rear pull-tabs for convenient on and off.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>A removable, molded PU-like EVA footbed with a textile topcover supplies excellent underfoot comfort. Vulcanized rubber midsoles deliver extra support and shock absorption. Herringbone rubber soles provide stable traction on slippery surfaces. These sneakers are available in several colors.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>These also run somewhat large.</p>
<p><strong></strong></p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07FBQRRSQ/" />
	</div>
	<p>These men's sneakers have a soft woven sock-knit fabric upper treated with advanced Hydro-Knit waterproof technology and leather-textured synthetic side panels for added stability.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> High-traction rubber outsoles are slip and oil resistant. Memory foam insoles provide long-lasting comfort and support.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>Some may find they could have more arch support.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07XBS9C52/" />
	</div>
	<p>These sneakers have a lightweight, waterproof knit upper that provides adaptive support for the best possible fit.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>Dual front and rear pull tabs allow for easy on and off. They're offered in men and women's sizes.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>They may feel a little hot.</p>
<p><strong></strong></p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rhinestone Anklets Are the Accessories You Didn&#8217;t Know You Needed</title>
		<author>Claudia Miller</author>		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 19:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<link>https://footwearnews.com/2020/shop/womens/best-rhinestone-anklets-1202898232/</link>
					<amzn:heroImage>https://pmcfootwearnews.files.wordpress.com/2020/01/loyata-anklet.jpg</amzn:heroImage>
							<amzn:heroImageCaption>Amazon</amzn:heroImageCaption>
					<amzn:indexContent>False</amzn:indexContent>
		<amzn:products>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B06VSLWXXD/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Kiokioa Charm Anklet]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Drip in (faux) diamonds with Kiokioa’s dazzling anklet.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[The Blingy One]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07PRVT9HM/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Loyata Dainty Ankle Bracelet]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Loyata’s anklet is an easy way to add charm to your outfit.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[The Dainty One]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B0742NYNT5/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[NYC Sterling Anklet Bracelet]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Try this elegant style in sapphire for a pop of color at the ankle.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[The Colorful One]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
				</amzn:products>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Anklets may have been popular in the &#8217;90s, but they&#8217;re making their way into our jewelry boxes again (and rightfully, so). Rhinestone styles can add a subtle dose of glam to basic office outfits or top off polished date-night looks when worn with pumps or heeled slide sandals. Many of today&#8217;s styles are prettier than ever, yet aren&#8217;t nearly as expensive as they look. Ahead, we&#8217;ve rounded up some of our favorite rhinestone-embellished anklets to make you feel like a million bucks. There are both gold and silver options so that you can find a style that suits your preference</p>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B06VSLWXXD/" />
	</div>
	<p>Kiokioa's anklet has layered rows of genuine crystals sitting atop a silver-plated base.</p>
<p><strong>Pros:</strong> This sleek rhinestone-embellished anklet stretches to fit around your ankle for a personalized fit.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>It may fit larger on smaller ankles.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07PRVT9HM/" />
	</div>
	<p>Loyata makes its anklet with a gold-plated brass chain and dangling cubic zirconium stones.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>This thin chain anklet is adorned with an adjustable clasp and dangling rhinestones for a dainty, subtle pop of charm.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>The chain or gems may get caught in the hem of raw-hem jeans and pants.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B0742NYNT5/" />
	</div>
	<p>NYC Sterling makes this anklet in gold-plated and silver versions with black, sapphire and clear rhinestones for multiple buying options.</p>
<p><strong style="font-family:-apple-system, BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen-Sans, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;">Pros: </strong><span style="font-family:-apple-system, BlinkMacSystemFont, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, Oxygen-Sans, Ubuntu, Cantarell, 'Helvetica Neue', sans-serif;">The rhinestones of this anklet make it a fun, colorful accessory that pops on the ankle.</span></p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>This anklet may be delicate and can break if pulled too hard.</p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Relive Your Summer Camp Days In These Braided Anklets</title>
		<author>Claudia Miller</author>		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 17:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<link>https://footwearnews.com/2020/shop/womens/best-braided-anklets-amazon-1202898727/</link>
					<amzn:heroImage>https://pmcfootwearnews.files.wordpress.com/2020/01/fancy-shiny-anklet.jpg</amzn:heroImage>
							<amzn:heroImageCaption>Amazon</amzn:heroImageCaption>
					<amzn:indexContent>False</amzn:indexContent>
		<amzn:products>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07S39TS1T/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Fancy Shiny String Ankle Bracelets]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Layer Fancy Shiny’s anklets for a boho-chic vibe.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[The Charm Anklet]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B07GL769K9/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Infinityee888 Opal Moonstone Anklet Bracelet]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Or consider this moonstone anklet.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[The Moonstone Anklet]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
					<amzn:product>
				<amzn:productURL>https://amazon.com/dp/B078HLKSPL/</amzn:productURL>
									<amzn:productHeadline><![CDATA[Jeka Waterproof Ankle Bracelets]]></amzn:productHeadline>
													<amzn:productSummary><![CDATA[Brace for the beach in Jeka’s waterproof anklets.]]></amzn:productSummary>
																	<amzn:award><![CDATA[The Waterproof Anklet]]></amzn:award>
							</amzn:product>
				</amzn:products>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For many of us, the highlight of our childhood summers was making friendship bracelets and anklets with friends, then showing off what we learned at camp about weaving the strings in special ways. To help bring those memories alive again, we found a selection of adorable braided anklets to incorporate into your lineup. Whether you need a waterproof anklet for your upcoming seaside vacation or you are simply looking to add a pop of color to your favorite white sneakers, the following options have you covered. Can&#8217;t decide which style you like best? Try wearing a few at the same time for a boho, layered look.</p>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07S39TS1T/" />
	</div>
	<p>Fancy Shiny's anklets feature dangling silver embellishments and colorful string.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>The braided string in these anklets are wax-coated to protect them from water, sand and more; there are three separate anklets in this pack so you can wear one individually or stack them.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>These have an adjustable band that stretches from 8 to 12 inches, so some may find it hard to find the right fit.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B07GL769K9/" />
	</div>
	<p>These anklets feature woven wax cords and an opal woven closure.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>This anklet is uniquely wrapped around five opal moonstones for an eye-catching take on a braided anklet.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>The brand states that due to the natural property of the stone and hand-carved nature, each of them might have a difference.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align:center;">
	<div data-itemtype="product">
		<a href="https://amazon.com/dp/B078HLKSPL/" />
	</div>
	<p>Jeka's anklets are made from woven cotton and wax, coming in a pack of six.</p>
<p><strong>Pros: </strong>These colorful anklets are made to withstand the elements so they won't get tarnished or worn from a day at the beach or a sweaty trip to the gym.</p>
<p><strong>Cons: </strong>These anklets must be tied for closure and can come loose if not tied properly.</p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
